<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Epitaph for One Love]]></title>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-10-02T00:12:03+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Shy]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-27 19:06]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-27-19-06/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:04+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-27-19-06</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Wed, 27 May 2015 19:06:05 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I like your picture of mathematics. It actually reminds me of an article of Atiyah, who also compares mathematics with architecture. I've attached it, in case you are interested. Creativity is a fascinating subject, it is the beauty and challenge of mathematics at the same time. When I was in Germany, I took part in a project about creativity. The goal was to write a book discussing this topic from the perspective of all kinds of subjects. There were articles about creativity and biology, creativity and law, creativity and religion, creativity and music ..., and I also wrote something about creativity and mathematics. Moreover, we interviewed scientists and artists about their opinion. It was interesting to compare the roles creativity plays, and we realized that although the subjects are very different, there are common features. For instance that it's mysterious how we get ideas, they seem to come out of nowhere. But really, thinking about it, we realize that there is a long process of preparation (sometimes unconscious); that's what you describe as hard work.
</p>


<p>
Last weekend, my sister told me that she wants to a PhD in mathematics. It was quite a surprise for me, since last time we spoke, she was uncertain what she wants to do. But now she seems to be really determined. From my point of view, I just want her to find something she loves, any subject really, but that it will be mathematics is of course wonderful. My sister is now finishing her second year, and she plans to do her master in England, maybe in Cambridge. I hope that one day, you'll be able to meet her. I think that you two would have lots of things to talk about, since your situations are somewhat similar; and since your are more senior, my sister could learn something from you :-D
</p>


<p>
Yes, I just finished marking. This time it was quick: I started yesterday morning, and now I'm already done! Maybe the exam was too easy, or maybe my students really understood something *daydream*, or maybe I really wanted to answer your question with YES, but I was very efficient this time :-) I'm glad it's over.
</p>


<p>
Great that you like Papillon. It's funny that you mention the end, that's also my favourite part of the movie. I just felt so happy, because he was so determined, and longing so much to be free. Talking about determination, I was also impressed by the part where he is suffering so much in prison, isolated, in a narrow room, with almost no food, but still he wouldn't say the name of his friend. That's true friendship...
</p>


<p>
No no, you're not making any fuss at all, I'm actually glad that I have someone to tell the story, it's much better than keeping it to myself. And thanks for your warm words, they went straight into my heart, where I will keep them as a treasure. Thank you :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-26 15:24]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-26-15-24/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:03+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-26-15-24</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, May 26, 2015 3:24 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Thank you so much for your reply, I always enjoy the way you talk about mathematics, it makes me feel encouraged and even enchanted sometimes:-) I consider doing mathematics as building a house, at first, you should build the fondation, this is something you should do with hard work, then the rest part of the house requires more other elements, like creativity. So I will go my way step by step with confidence.
</p>


<p>
I am happy that you tell me the story, in case you feel I'm making fuss, I shall say nothing except that: I believe you will do your best :-)
</p>


<p>
Speaking of old-fashioned, it's funny that this is the word I often use to describe myself, so I am glad I find a companion :-) Compared with kindle, I prefer the real books in fact, I enjoy the feeling of holding a book and turning the pages, which makes me feel tranquil. Anyway, hope you a good luck in the chinatown. By the way, have you finished marking?
</p>


<p>
I have wathched Papillon this weekend, I really like it, espacially the end of the movie. When he jumped into the sea with a bag of coconut shell, I think he got the real freeness no matter he succeeded or not...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-24 23:43]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-24-23-43/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:02+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-24-23-43</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Dimanche 24 Mai 2015 23:43:14
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I strongly believe that you can realize your dream of becoming a real mathematician. People seem to agree that the most important ingredients are hard work, passion and curiosity, and I see all these things in you. Of course there are other things like talent or luck, but these are not in our control. Actually, I never considered myself very talented. Luck I had several times, but everyone will get chances, so that's very normal. Honestly, I don't think that I did anything special, everyone can do it. And concerning your feeling that there is still a long way, yes, indeed, the way is long and not always easy, but every way consists of many many little steps, it's the same for everyone. I guess it's just important to keep moving, to be positive and to believe in yourself. And then, things will work out for you.
</p>


<p>
Here is the story behind this fifth talk: Some time ago, I was invited to apply for a professorship in Germany (starting in late 2016). It's at a good university, and I have great respect for one of the colleagues working there, it would be awesome to work with him. So I thought, I'd give it a try. Not that I'm unhappy here in London, it's just that the conditions in Germany are better, that's why it's so hard to get a permanent position there. Anyway, I applied, and didn't think too much about it since there is very little chance of success. However, when I was in Shanghai, I got a message saying that I made it into the second round, which means that I've been invited to give a talk and to an interview. That's the talk I mentioned. I still think that success is unlikely, but I'd like to try my best. To be honest, I haven't told anyone about this, not my colleagues, not even my parents or my sister, simply because it's unlikely, and I don't want to make a fuss. Please do me a favour and keep it as a secret, at least for now.
</p>


<p>
A Kindle? Do you like it? It's very convenient, of course. But is it the same feeling as a book? Maybe it's just me being old-fashioned :-) Anyway, I think I'll go to a bookstore in Chinatown, and try my luck there. I'll do it after I finished marking my exams. Marking is a horrible job, I really dislike it, so I need something nice to look forward to.
</p>


<p>
"And I wait for your reply just like a child wait for her present." You are so cute :-) Right now, several things are happening which might have a huge influence on my life. But one event stands out: That I have met you.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-24 13:52]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-24-13-52/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:01+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-24-13-52</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Sunday, May 24, 2015 1:52 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Reading your email can always put a big smile on my face, just like you said :-D And I wait for your reply just like a child wait for her present.
</p>


<p>
I feel that I have still a long way to go to become a real mathematician, maybe like you. But I really want to be one and I will try my best, your encouragement means a lot to me, thank you so much! Yes, I think giving a talk is also a way to help yourself understand better, I learned a lot last summer in Wuhan, we gave the talk in turns and discuss together, that's a good way to learn something. Talking about giving a lecture, your talk in Wuhan three weeks ago is great! I like it very much :-D (And, writing about this, I'm surprised to find out there are just two weeks since we said goodbye in Wuhan, time moves really slow indeed...) Your 5th talk will be a kind of special? Why?
</p>


<p>
In fact, the winner in Friday is one of my classmates in Master 2, now she's doing Phd in B too, but she does algebra and her talk is about the Hilbert series of pro-p group which I know few. But I am sure you know a lot.
</p>


<p>
As far as I know, buying Chinese literature in Europe is not an easy thing, I know a online Chinese bookstore in UK called Behomy, but I never tried, it has the same problem that there aren't many selections. However, in China, there are many good choices, I can find almost all the books I need in 当当 and Amazon china and the delivery is quite fast, maybe just two days I suppose, but it seems impossible to send the books to Europe. So every time I go back to China, I will bring some books to here, but the problem is it's a bit heavy... So, there is another choice. I bought a Kindle :-) The electronic edition of most of Chinese literature is available in Amazon China.
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-23 22:06]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-23-22-06/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-23-22-06</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Sat, 23 May 2015 22:06:32 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I just want to say: Thank you, R, that you exist! Thank you so much! You make me happy. It's incredible, when I read an email from you, I feel like the happiest person in the world, but that feeling doesn't last very long, only until I get the next email from you, which makes me even happier :-)
</p>


<p>
I look forward, no, it is my dearest wish, to see you again. Why can't late August be already tomorrow? We talked about that time passes very quickly. But this is relative, if there is something we are longing for, then the time we have to wait can be extremely long, it never seems to pass. And three months is a very long time... I guess what helps is that we both will be busy over the summer: You will have this intensive working seminar in Wuhan, and an interesting conference in Copenhagen (these are the activities I know of); and I will go to four conferences, so that I will give four talks. In addition, I will give another fifth talk in some sort of seminar, but it's a bit special, and I really want to give a very good talk. So that will require some serious preparation. Concerning your visa, just make sure that you know the application procedure, and that you get your passport back immediately, so that you can travel directly afterwards. As always with these organizational things, they are annoying because they require time and energy, but in the end, they usually work out. So I'm sure you'll manage. Please keep me updated, so that we can make more concrete plans when the time is ripe. How wonderful it will be to meet you again...
</p>


<p>
Can I ask you a stupid question? What is the best way to buy Chinese books in Europe? Is it possible to do that online, so that the book is sent to my address? I tried some time ago, and realized that it's a non-trivial matter. For instance, European or American amazon has only a small selection of Chinese literature, and they are sold by some shops which might not be reliable. Do you know a better way?
</p>


<p>
It's great for PhD students to come together, and to give and listen to talks. What topics were the talks about? Anything in mathematics, or was the area more restricted? And what was the topic of the winner? Yes, giving a lesson seems like a very good idea. As long as it doesn't take too much time, it's good to practice giving talks. And usually, teaching helps to understand yourself. Actually, at some point, I'd like to listen to a talk by you about your research. Isn't that a wonderful thought? I'm confident that it will happen, and it would make me feel proud. You are very clever and hard-working, so just keep it up, and you'll do well :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-22 20:39]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-22-20-39/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:59+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-22-20-39</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Friday, May 22, 2015 8:39 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
You are so nice and sweet! I'm happy that you still remember my question :-) In fact, I also looked up something about boomerang in the internet, but it explains in a professional way, I still couldn't understand after I read... So, thank you for your answer :-D.
</p>


<p>
I have read the poem of Hardy and the translation by Xu, it's really beautiful, then I can't stop reading them for several times...
</p>


<p>
You know, your email doesn't stop me being overexcited, but makes me even more exicited! And thank you very much for your generous offer, you give me so many good reasons that I can't even say no, so I guess I should accept it :-) Ok, back to reality, I'm thinking about applying my visa in the early July in Paris maybe one or two days before I take the plane back to China, because Besancon is a small city, there is no embassy. I hope everything will be fine.
</p>


<p>
Ah, ok, Papillion, I haven't heard it before, but it seems great, cause I watched The Shawshank Redemption few years ago which has the similar theme, and I love it, and I think your recommendation is even better, so I will watch it anyway.
</p>


<p>
Today, we went to "la journée de l'école doctorale" in D, some Ph.D. students gave interesting talks, and it's a good opportunity for me to learn how to give a lecture in French, because I thinking about giving a lesson next semester. And it's funny that the jury gave the winner 150€ as a gift.
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-21 21:30]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-21-21-30/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:58+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-21-21-30</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Thu, 21 May 2015 21:30:21 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
and you have also said exactly the words I'd like to say :-) I also consider myself lucky that I can do what I really love to do. My work is for me just like a hobby, which I do out of interest and which I'm able to do for a living. This is actually one of the other main topics of Steve Job's Stanford speech I told you about; he said "You've got to find what you love. And that is as true for your work as it is for your lovers. Your work is going to fill a large part of your life, and the only way to be truly satisfied is to do what you believe is great work. And the only way to do great work is to love what you do. If you haven't found it yet, keep looking. Don't settle." It's so true. I'm happy it works for me. And I'm equally happy that you have found the same happiness :-)
</p>


<p>
Oh, if you could come to London in late August, that would be wonderful, truly great. Really, I mean it. London has a lot to offer, I could show you around, and we could go to Oxford, it's just a train ride away. But don't get overexcited, most likely, the dining hall in Christ Church will still be closed ;-) I guess it also applies to me; I have to stop myself from getting too excited, since you still have to sort out the visa issue. I hope that it'll be easy, and please let me know if I can be of any help. Before I forget: I'm going on vacation in Portugal with my parents and my sister from 1 September to 8 September, so planning your visit for late August is fine, but not later. Also, I'd be more than happy to pay for all your expenses and book accommodation on campus for you. The main reason is that I'd really love to do that from the bottom of my heart. But a more practical reason is that I have a grant which started this year, and a computation has shown that I have spent way to little money, although I already had this big trip to China and two visitors. So to save me some trouble, please do accept the offer.
</p>


<p>
Thanks for the poem, I like it a lot. Xu Zhimo also translated some English poems, for instance "A Week" by Hardy, very beautiful.
</p>


<p>
Actually, I meant another movie. It's just called Papillon, without Le, and it's older, from 1973. It's about a guy who has to go to prison for a crime he didn't commit. He then tries to escape ... Or in other words, it's about the desire to be free. I quite like it, maybe you would like it, too.
</p>


<p>
I like Harry Potter as well. Perhaps it's the child in everyone of us. Children have something fascinating and beautiful, they are without sorrows; I often have to smile when watching them play. Talking about playing, I looked up why a boomerang comes back, the secret is that the legs spin with different speed. Sorry if this sounds stupid, but I really liked that you asked me this question, and the way you asked it. So sweet :-) Maybe someone else would not have paid attention, but I somehow have kept this little incident as a memory, and now I'm caring it with me all the time ...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-21 12:16]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-21-12-16/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:57+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-21-12-16</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Thursday, May 21, 2015 12:16 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
In fact, your passion for mathematics also gives me energy for what I am doing now, and I feel lucky that I could work with things I'm really interested in.
</p>


<p>
Your description about the day in Oxford also makes me enchanted, and anyway, I really want to go there by myself. :-) Yes, you are right, I am a fan of Harry Potter since I was a child, for me, the magic world in it is one of the most important memories of my childhood. So your Oxford trip makes me feel excited like a child! I'm thinking about maybe I could go to London in the late August, and then visit a friend in Reading, but I should ask the visa issues first.
</p>


<p>
"These people were great artists because they had tragic lives, or they had tragic lives because they were great artists", you have said exactly the words that I want to say. And that's the reason why I like these people so much, I am so happy that you feel the same! There was a romance between 徐志摩 and 林徽因, A Snowflake's Happiness is one his poems, written to LIN, have you read?
</p>


<p>
You mean Le Papillon? The story of a smart little girl and an old man? yes, I love it, quite warm and funny :-D By the way, "the children version" of Dead Poets Society we have talked about, its name is Les Choristes.
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-20 00:17]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-20-00-17/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:56+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-20-00-17</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mercredi 20 Mai 2015 00:17:43
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
it makes me feel warm and happy that you share my passion for mathematics. Thank you! :-)
</p>


<p>
I just came back from Oxford. Since it was my first time in Oxford, I took a bit of time before my seminar talk to walk around. Among other things, I was at the Christ Church, where they shot scenes for Harry Potter. Unfortunately, the dining hall was closed for visitors. Then I met with my host and gave a seminar talk. Afterwards, we had dinner in St John's College. That was like in the movies, or like turning back time. The ceilings were high, on the walls were paintings of important members of the college, people were wearing gowns, and there were prayers in Latin. I still feel enchanted ... By the way, do you like Harry Potter a lot? I saw that your skype username has h in it ...
</p>


<p>
I have the same feeling as you about artists like 萧红 or 林徽因. Not only were their lives short, but - at least from what I read - full of strong emotions, and tragic love. Even more extreme is 顾城. When I first read his story and how it ended, I was very emotional and felt extremely sad. I wonder whether these people were great artists because they had tragic lives, or they had tragic lives because they were great artists. Talking about 林徽因, I found out that she was close to 徐志摩. I have recently read a few poems he wrote, some of them are very beautiful, I like them a lot.
</p>


<p>
Actually, I haven't watched A Beautiful Mind yet. But since you like it so much, I will watch it; it's on top of my To-do list. I'm sure that you know more movies than me, which is good, because then I can ask you for recommendations :-D The other day, I also had a movie in mind which you probably like, its name is Papillon. Do you know it?
</p>


<p>
Yes, I'm going to the Symposium, which is for five days in the first half of August. The rest of August I will be in London.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-18 17:23]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-18-17-23/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:55+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-18-17-23</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Monday, May 18, 2015 5:23 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Your desprition of mathematics is just as wonderful as it should be! You could really appreciate the beauty of mathematics. And, you have choosed really great movies! In fact,I have heard something about the movie Imitation game from one of my friends the other day, and I thought you might like it because you told me that you are interested in number theory. What a coincidence, you tell me today that you have already watched and like it! Speak of the movie about mathematicians, I think The beautiful mind is also great, of course you have watched it cause it is classical.
</p>


<p>
Yes, when reading about the life of 萧红, it aways makes me feel a kind of regretful, she has the talent in literature, however she lived in a wrong time. And I have the same feeling about 林徽因 whom we have already talked about. Why does beautiful life awalys so short! As for the work of 萧红, I haven't read one before, but 呼兰河传 is one of her most famous novels I think, maybe you could have a try.
</p>


<p>
I wasn't lucky as you were during the long flight last week, the little tele in my seat was broken, it doesn't work at all... :-)
</p>


<p>
I haven't decided yet where to go after the conference in Copenhagen. Do you have a symposium in Norway in August? Will you go back to London after that or you have other plans?
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-18 10:47]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-18-10-47/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:54+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-18-10-47</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Lundi 18 Mai 2015 10:47:32
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, exactly as you wrote, I arrived safely in London last night. Usually, I really hate long flights, but I was lucky this time with the movie selection. I watched The Imitation Game about Alan Turing, The Theory of Everything about Stephen Hawkings and 黄金时代 about 萧红. All these characters made an impression on me, especially their creativity. Mathematics is actually a very creative subject. I think about it as colours of the rainbow: The two extremes are red and violet, but somehow they belong together. Mathematics is also positioned at two extreme points, it is the most logical of all sciences, but also as creative as an art. And these two aspects belong together, one cannot be without the other. Unfortunately, this is sometimes difficult to explain to non-mathematicians. Coming back to 萧红, she must have been a very interesting character, who had a (short) life full of ups and downs. I think I'd like to read something she wrote. Do you know some of her work?
</p>


<p>
In the UK, every PhD student has to be examined every year. This is to give them feedback on their progress. So I'm going to examine someone else's student today.
</p>


<p>
Is there a particular place you would like to go for vacation this summer?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes, and a nice week for you as well,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-17 15:44]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-17-15-44/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:53+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-17-15-44</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Sunday, May 17, 2015 3:44 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I suppose that you will arrive London tonight, hope everything will be fine. Yes, that is exactly the conference I'm talking about, I have already signed up, since it will begin on 16th August, I have to return France as soon as the seminar in Wuhan ends. So no time for a vacation in Wuhan, but, as you have said, it's worth it. And I'm thinking about maybe I could have a vacation somewhere after that.
</p>


<p>
It seems that you enjoy your stay in Shanghai, although I can't stand the skyscraper, but I really like the bike tour! However, It's a kind of hard to enjoy due to the crowdedness and traffic in the big city of China :-)
</p>


<p>
You have mentioned you are going to examine a PHD student, are you going to have a student or something? And I wish you could spend your next week smoothly.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-16 14:50]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-16-14-50/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:52+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-16-14-50</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Sat, 16 May 2015 14:50:27 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I'm delighted to hear that you arrived safely. Enjoy the fresh air, the empty (or almost empty) streets and the quietness. And yes, Copenhagen is a great place, in particular for operator algebras. I know quite a few people there. Are you talking about this conference "Young Mathematicians in C*-Algebras"? That would be great. Haagerup is famous, and the other speaker, Stuart White, is also very good and gives very nice talks. So, yes, you should go.
</p>


<p>
Today is my last night in Shanghai. I really enjoyed my stay here. Apart from mathematics, we also went to Shanghai and had a look around. We went up on this skyscraper which used to be the tallest. It is about 470 meters high, and we were on the top floor. Do you feel shaky reading these lines? I was OK up there, but I was also quite happy when we were down on the ground again. They have now built a taller building, more than 600 meters high, next to it. It is a crazy way to spend money... We also had a bike tour in Shanghai. I'm quite proud that I survived ;-)
</p>


<p>
All in all, I really enjoyed my visit to China. I got lots of inspiration, and will return to London with many many precious memories. This should give me enough energy to carry me through sleepness nights answering students' emails...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-15 16:58]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-15-16-58/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:51+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-15-16-58</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Friday, May 15, 2015 4:58 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I arrived B yesterday, everything goes fine. And I'am happy that I can breath the fresh air again! Today one of my colleague told me there is a Mini-course in Copenhagen during the summer vacation, one of the major speaker is Haagerup, I think it's interesting, maybe I will try to sign up.
</p>


<p>
Have you finished your trip in Shanghai? But it seems that you have to throw yourself into the really busy week as soon as you go back to London. 100 email each day?! That makes me hard to imagine how can you respond all of them :-) Anyway, wish you a good luck.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-14 01:34]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-14-01-34/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:50+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-14-01-34</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Jeudi 14 Mai 2015 01:34:00
<br>
Objet: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I'm glad that your father is well. Your parents must be very proud of you; they are fortunate to have such a daughter like you :-)
</p>


<p>
You are a detailed observer. Yes, I wake up early, but I also go to bed early, so that's OK. My talk yesterday was good. It was similar to the one I gave in Wuhan, so preparation was easy.
</p>


<p>
When I get back to London, my first week will be very busy: On Monday, I have to examine a PhD student, on Tuesday, I'm giving a seminar talk in Oxford, and the exam for my own lectures takes place on Friday. Last year, shortly before the exam, my students sent me 100 emails each day with questions about the exam. And directly after the exam, I spent several days doing nothing else but sleeping, drinking, eating and marking exams. I fear that this year, I have to get prepared for a similar battle. Once that is done, I can enjoy life again ...
</p>


<p>
Good luck with the paper!
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-13 19:41]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-13-19-41/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:49+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-13-19-41</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Wednesday, May 13, 2015 1:41 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I notice that you get up quite early, I hope you have got over the jet-lag :-). I'm glad to hear that the interesting talk tomorow gave you some inspiration, and how was your talk today morning?
</p>


<p>
Thank you for your concern, my father has finished the small operation today, the result turns out to be quite succesful, so I think I can leave at ease tomorrow.
</p>


<p>
Hopefully, some improvements could be made with the paper I'm working on in the next two mouths in B :-) After that, I hope I could arrange myself a trip, maybe I would have a chance to meet you... Well, a lot plans, I expect that they all could be realised!
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-13 06:06]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-13-06-06/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:48+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-13-06-06</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mercredi 13 Mai 2015 06:06:26
<br>
Objet: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
a new sister! Wow! Awesome! This trip to China is exceeding all my expectations. Honestly, before I left London, I was very uncertain what to expect, especially from my visit to Wuhan. I would never have imagined that I would come back to London having found a new sister. What a wonderful world.
</p>


<p>
As we discussed, life is full of coincidences and wonders. Actually, I originally wanted to visit Wuhan in the week after Shanghai, and we would have missed each other. Also, there were problems with my visa. So it was by chance that things worked out. Thinking about it, I feel amazed how little control we have over the things that happen in our lives. At the same time, this makes me realize that we should really make use of the few chances we get.
</p>


<p>
Thanks for adding me in Skype. I accepted, so we can skype whenever you feel like it. Just let me know.
</p>


<p>
I'm having a good time in Shanghai. Yesterday there was a very interesting talk, and I hope that I can use some of the material for my own research. Today it's my turn to give a talk.
</p>


<p>
I hope that you are having a few nice days back at home with your parents. Didn't you say that your father had to do some sort of operation? I hope that everything went well and that he is doing fine. If I'm not mistaken, you are going back to France tomorrow. Of course, I wish you a safe trip, or: "Gute Reise" :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-11 22:54]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-22-54/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:47+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-22-54</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Monday, May 11, 2015 4:54 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I am really excited to have a new brother! Yes, you are really good, don't be modest, that's the reality :-). I have the same feeling as you do, maybe we have many things in common. Speak of last week, I should thank Q for giving me the chance to know you and talk to you, I really cherish it, there isn't any inconvenience at all. So you are welcome anytime, I mean it. Maybe I can find a chance to go to London, I am expecting it.
</p>


<p>
Yes, S also does maths, he took M2 in Paris last year, but he changed his direction to f this year and went to B. In fact, I feel that you have much in common :-)
</p>


<p>
By the way, I have sent you a request for adding in Skype, hope you have well recieved it.
</p>


<p>
Bonne nuit,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-11 22:04]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-22-04/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:46+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-22-04</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Lundi 11 Mai 2015 22:04:43
<br>
Objet: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
you are really nice. If you keep making me compliments like that, one day I will lose my sense of reality ;-) More seriously, I think one of the best things about being a mathematician is that you can travel around and meet interesting people. And I think that people are the biggest source of inspiration. But then, it is not easy to find others with similar ideas and points of view. With you, I had that feeling of being close, almost like brother and sister. Actually, what a wonderful thought: To have you as my second sister! I hope you do not mind that I think about you that way...
</p>


<p>
My skype username is t_x. But I am offline almost all the time, so you would have to let me know in advance if you would like to talk.
</p>


<p>
S? Hmmm, that is indeed funny, what a coincidence :-) Is he also doing maths? I am sure that I will like him. First, I thought that it would be great to visit you guys in B. But then thinking about it again, I realized that I would cause inconveniences; and I have already caused so many inconveniences for you last week in Wuhan that it will be difficult to pay back. Maybe it would really be better if you and S could visit me in London, so that I can be the host...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-11 13:08]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-13-08/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:45+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-13-08</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Monday, May 11, 2015 7:08 AM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
How generous you are! I feel really happy that I can make a friend like you and I enjoy writting to you. In fact, I have been using skype for few years, you can tell me your username that I can add you.
</p>


<p>
It will be nice if it is possible for you to pay a visit to B, it is a small but beautiful city, I can also introduce my boyfriend to you there, his name is S (has the same pronunciation as your name in Germany :-) ), I think you will also like him.
</p>


<p>
I agree with your opinion on the internet, it makes our lives more convenient, but in the meantime, it also makes us less willing to think. In the past, we communicated by letter in which we put a lot of thought, so is the email today. However, if we communicate in other ways, like "Wechat", it is less thoughtful.
</p>


<p>
Well, hope you have a good trip in Shanghai :-D.
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
