<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Epitaph for One Love]]></title>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-10-04T03:13:42+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Shy]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-23 13:12]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-23-13-12/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:34+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-23-13-12</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Dimanche 23 Août 2015 13:12:13
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Good. Thanks for letting me know. By the way, for the Eurostar, you have to check-in at least 30min before the departure, so allow enough time and make sure not to miss it :-b Just joking, I am sure you know and will be there in time :-) It's good that everything is fine.
</p>


<p>
See you later,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-23 11:49]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-23-11-49/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:33+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-23-11-49</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Sunday, August 23, 2015 11:49 AM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
I have arrived Bd, and I'm waiting for the connecting train at 13h25. Everything is fine :-) I bought the ticket for eurostar 9047 which will arrive at 18h30 (local time) at the "LONDRES ST-PANCRAS".
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-23 12:13]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-23-12-13/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:32+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-23-12-13</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Dimanche 23 Août 2015 12:13:31
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Are you on the train now? Have you decided how to travel from Paris? Let me know if you need help. And if you like, you can call me whenever it is convenient for you.
</p>


<p>
Don't worry to much about it. These things happen. I'm sure that in the end, you'll make it, and everything will be fine :-)
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-23 10:21]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-23-10-21/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:31+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-23-10-21</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: X L
<br>
Sent: Sunday, August 23, 2015 10:21 AM
<br>
To: r.x@e.fr
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
OK. Before you book your flight: I was just thinking that maybe, you could still take the Eurostar, even if it is more expensive. The reason is that it would be more convenient, and also, it will be reimbursed anyway. I leave it up to you. Just think about it, and let me know.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-23 10:15]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-23-10-15/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:30+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-23-10-15</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Sunday, August 23, 2015 10:15 AM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
My train will arrive at 15h37 at Paris gare de Lyon.
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-22 20:50]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-22-20-50/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:29+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-22-20-50</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Samedi 22 Août 2015 20:50:07
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, I agree, the most important thing is that we can finally meet again; everything else is secondary, or in other words, we'll make things work out as we are together :-)
</p>


<p>
It's great that you enjoyed the conference in Copenhagen. It seems that you've seen more of the city than me :-) I have only been there for a research visit, which was very productive. While that is good, it also means that I didn't have time for other things apart from maths :-( Well, I'm sure that overall, you had a very very interesting summer, and I look forward to hear more about it. At the same time, you must have worked a lot, and you have been traveling non-stop recently. So it is good to have a break, enjoy some holidays, and relax a bit :-)
</p>


<p>
Now, in less than a day I will finally see you again :-D :-D :-D I look forward to welcoming you, the thought of it alone makes me sooo happy, and soon, it is really and finally going to happen :-) So, have a safe journey, and: See you tomorrow!!
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-21 22:41]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-21-22-41/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:28+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-21-22-41</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Friday, August 21, 2015 10:41 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Yes, I will arrive on Sunday (23 August) at 15:30 at London St-Pancras, it's really nice to see you again :-) And I have checked the weather forecast in London, it seems that it will rain all the days in next weak, so surely, I will bring an umbrella :-) For me, it is already a great pleasure to spend the week with you, so it would be fun anyway no matter we could find the places or not :-D
</p>


<p>
Today is the end of the workshop, and last talk by Stuart White was cancelled for some reasons, so I got some time to go around the city, we took a boat tour in Copenhagen, and after the dinner, we walked along the river. I'm glad to come to this conference, the talks are good and I also meet a lot of people here. Tomorrow I will come back to B, and the day after tomorrow I can go to London finally :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-20 23:28]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-20-23-28/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:27+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-20-23-28</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Jeudi 20 Août 2015 23:28:48
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, I share your feelings, I have also been waiting for your visit for a long long time, the desire to see you again grows every day ... And I am sure that your wish will come true. We will definitely find a way so that I can also visit you. It is so kind of you to have this wish! Indeed, I really hope that we will see each other often in the future, because I want to be with you :-)
</p>


<p>
Well, maybe it is better not to have high expectations on my abilities as a guide. I mean, I will try my best, obviously. But as I wrote, in my case, it is already a success if I manage to find the places we want to go to ;-) In all these plannings, one thing I have no influence on is the weather. So that is why it would be good if you could bring an umbrella. It might sound stupid, but I always have the feeling that if one doesn't bring an umbrella, then it will rain for sure :-D Moreover, if you want, and if it is possible, you could also bring all your receipts (for visa, travel, ...) so that we can sort out reimbursement while you are here. And yes, your plans for 31 August sound good, taking a train at around one or two in the afternoon will be fine. Concerning your question on exchanging money, that will be no problem at all, London is full of banks, there is even a tube station called Bank; this means that even a guy like me will find one ;-) When I need foreign money, I usually just go to an ATM and use the credit card provided by my German bank. If you have that, too, then it's even easier. In any case, we can always just go to a bank.
</p>


<p>
Oh, before I forget, just let me make sure: You are arriving on Sunday (23 August) at 15:30 at London St Pancras, with a Eurostar, right? I will then pick you up at the station :-)
</p>


<p>
So, is the conference going well? And when are you going back, on Saturday?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-19 22:40]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-19-22-40/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:26+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-19-22-40</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Wednesday, August 19, 2015 10:40 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I'm sure you have made very good plans for our trip, and I'm also really happy that I could spend my one-week vacation with you in the summer and I've expected it for such a long time :-) Moreover, I also wish that you could visit me after, in B or in Wuhan, and then I can arrange the trip for you :-)
</p>


<p>
Here is my telephone: +33 7 ** ** ** **. I have noted down your number and your address just in case and thank you for these information, you are very thoughtful :-) For the plans in 31 August, since my friend's time is very flexible, she stays in Reading all the days in the August and September, so she told me that I can choose anytime for the train to there, and just phone her before I get on the train. She also told me that I could just buy the ticket before the departure, I've searched in Virgin trains, there is a train every 10 min, so that would be convenient I think :-) Concerning that you should take the airplane at 18:45, I think maybe sometime around one or two o'clock would be good, maybe? There is one more thing, the day I came back to B from Wuhan, I went to the bank to exchange euros to pounds, but the bank told me that there are no pounds in B and they need to get them from Paris and it takes 10 days, finally, I didn't get what I want. So I need to exchange after I arrive London, could you please take me to the bank or some other place where I could get the pounds maybe?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-19 18:34]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-19-18-34/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:25+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-19-18-34</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mercredi 19 Août 2015 18:34:15
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
it is great that you are enjoying the conference, and that you like the talks. I am sure that you can learn a lot. And yes, Muenster is a special place. The research group is huge and of very high quality, and there is lots of funding available. That is why I think that academically, I grew up in paradise :-) Thinking back, I will of course keep my time in Muenster in very good memory. At the same time, I am also glad that I moved somewhere else, because now that I realize how special Muenster is, I can appreciate it even more, and I can also become more independent.
</p>


<p>
You are so nice, and simply too polite :-) As I wrote, making these arrangements is part of the fun, and it is a great pleasure for me to prepare for your visit :-D And no worries, to be on the safe side, I have already bought tickets for the drama and the musical on Monday. So everything is fine. You know, I am just so happy that you can come to visit. It will be truly wonderful to see you again :-) By agreeing to come, and by sorting out all these issues with your visa and your travel arrangements, you have already made your contribution, and I am more than happy to do my part :-)
</p>


<p>
Yes, I feel the same about visiting places and becoming part of stories; in some sense, it feels like that the stories become alive. And to add to that, I also think that once we have visited the places we want to visit, we will keep them in our memories and think about them differently, so that in some sense, these places become part of our own story...
</p>


<p>
I don't think we will need them, but let us exchange mobile phone numbers, just in case. Mine is +44 754 *******.
</p>


<p>
Also, again just to be on the safe side, let me give you the address and phone number of my office:
<br>
X L
<br>
School of Mathematical Sciences
<br>
?? University of London
<br>
?? Road
<br>
London E* ***
<br>
phone: +44 20 **** ****
</p>


<p>
And here is my private address:
<br>
X L
<br>
21A G*******
<br>
London E** ***
<br>
</p>


<p>
Moreover, may I ask: Have you now made concrete plans for 31 August, after your visit? I am flying back to Germany on 31 August in the evening, at 18:45, so I will have plenty of time.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-18 23:17]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-18-23-17/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:24+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-18-23-17</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, August 18, 2015 11:17 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
The course by the main speakers are very nice and there are really a lot of people coming here, I'm sure Munster has a big group for oa, it seems to me that if I ask a guy where does he comes from, the answer is always Munster :-)
</p>


<p>
It is really nice of you that you make all this arrangements :-) and I'm sure that you will take me to a very lovely place, I'm looking forward to see it, in fact, I've already begun to think about what kind of place it will be, there are many pictures in my head now :-) Yes, when some place is related to a story, it will always makes me excited that if I could visit that place as if I become part of the story and I could better understand the feeling of people in the story. I searched "War horse" in the internet, yes, it is a really moving story, if we get the time, maybe we could watch it, but I'm not sure time permits or not, and by the way, should we buy the ticket now for the musical and drama? Maybe I can do it in the internet now, you've done lots of the things for our trips, so I hope I could also contribute at least a little bit to it :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-17 21:36]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-17-21-36/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:23+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-17-21-36</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Lundi 17 Août 2015 21:36:14
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
oh, your journey to Copenhagen really sounds like an odyssey ;-) Hopefully, the way back will be better. So, how was the first day? And have you met many people?
</p>


<p>
"A Midsummer Night's Dream" sounds great. Let's go to that. Another drama which sounds nice is "War Horse". Have you read the description? I found out that there was a movie about the same novel. Both the movie and the drama are supposed to be very moving. But I don't know whether you would like it. Anyway, now we already have "Matilda" and "A Midsummer Night's Dream". We can decide together whether we would like to watch "War Horse" as well. Let's see.
</p>


<p>
I have bought train tickets, for three trips, to Oxford, Cambridge, and another one. The third one is to a place I like very much, and I want you to see it as well. You will know when we get there. I won't tell you more right now, because if you don't mind, I'd like to make it a little surprise :-) Talking about Cambridge, I am really glad that we decided to go there, because I suddenly remembered a novel I read a long time ago. It was written by Christopher Wilkins and is called "The Measure of Love". It also appeared under the title "The Horizontal Instrument", but I like the first title better. It is about a very moving love story, and it begins in Cambridge :-) Another reason I look forward to the trip...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-16 23:31]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-16-23-31/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:22+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-16-23-31</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Sunday, August 16, 2015 11:31 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I have just arrived at Copenhagen tonight, I took the train with another phd student at 10 clock in the morning at B and arrived here at 10 in the night... It first takes one hour for us we find the right train from airport to the nearest train station and then since our GPS don't work here, it takes another two hours to find the hotel :-( And what's more, the room in the hotel in extremely small for four people... Anyway, I'm sure the talks tomorrow will be interesting which will make all these troubles worthwhile :-)
</p>


<p>
I have gone through the list for the dramas again, I think that "1984" and "The mid-summer night's dream" are good for me, which one do you prefer? Or do you have some other dramas you would like to watch? And I also noticed that there will be a drama about Harry Potter :-) But it will begin until next year and also one about Odyssey which will play in September.
</p>


<p>
Yes, I remember the scenes of the movie, after I saw this film, my desire to visit Cambridge grows much stronger :-) Oh, you have already finished "The Heart of Midlothian"? That's good, then you can find something else to read and continue your reading list :-) Last time you told me that you began to read this book, I also said that I read Der Zauberberg at that time, but after that, I don't find the time to read anymore, but I've taken it with me to France, so I could continue it now :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-15 20:26]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-15-20-26/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:21+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-15-20-26</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Samedi 15 Août 2015 20:26:28
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I'm glad to know that you arrived safely, and that you have solved your problem in a better way than last time :-) Hopefully, you have recovered a bit from the journey, which must have been exhausting. It seems that you will be busy again, since you are going to Copenhagen next week, aren't you? But the conference will surely be very interesting, and you'll meet many of my friends and colleagues. So I wish you good success, and also fun :-D
</p>


<p>
At least, the weather is probably nicer, not so hot and humid as in Wuhan. And although the weather is hard to predict, what I can say is that when you come to London, it will definitely not be too hot ;-) Speaking about London, there is only one week to go. That sounds wonderful, doesn't it? I'm making concrete plans now, and I'll probably buy some train tickets soon :-) Speaking about choices for dramas, the list is indeed very long. But I just had a look at it again, and found out that many of the items on that list will only be shown at some point after your visit. For the dates of your visit, I have counted about 20 dramas. Just look at the last line of the summary for each drama, and you will see the date. So this reduces the choices and makes it a bit easier, I hope :-)
</p>


<p>
Yes, the movie about Hawking and his former wife is very impressive indeed. And I also had a positive feeling afterwards. Hope and love are truly beautiful and powerful feelings, and I am always amazed what these positive feelings can achieve. By the way, maybe you still remember some of the scenes of the movie, because many of them were filmed in Cambridge, where we will go :-) I have finished this book "The Heart of Midlothian" of Walter Scott I told you about. It was also very moving, and in a sense positive, too. The main story is about a young woman called Jeanie. Her sister is accused of a crime she didn't commit, and she is sentenced to death. So Jeanie decides to walk (!) from Edinburgh to London in order to get a pardon for her sister from the Queen...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-14 22:30]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-14-22-30/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:20+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-14-22-30</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Friday, August 14, 2015 10:30 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I've arrived B yesterday night, everything goes fine except a small unluckiness, the train I took to B was more than one hour late, which made me missed the latest bus to the campus again... But at least, things was not as bad as last time, since Q and his family went back to China for a vacation, he asked one of the new students who came to B this summer to live at his home to look after his cat :-) So I contacted that girl and spent the night at Q's house which is just near the train station.
</p>


<p>
I also watched "The theory of everything" during the flight, it is really a movie that can make me think a lot after watching. In fact, everyone of us has the limits, physically or mentally, but we could always find our own way to overcome them, just like what Hawking said in the movie, as long as we live, there is hope. I also like the love between Hawing and his former wife in the movie, although they don't end up together in the end, this doesn't change the beauty of it.
</p>


<p>
Yes, Greenwich Park, how can I forgot it :-) Of course I would like to go. It seems that you know lots of parks in London, which is good :-) I looked the list of dramas in London today, there are indeed many good ones, and it's hard to choose among them :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-12 13:57]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-12-13-57/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:19+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-12-13-57</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mercredi 12 Août 2015 13:57:12
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
OK, we will do all the things that you want to do :-D I like your choices, in particular, Primrose Hill. Really, I had to smile when I read it, because it is my favourite place in London, and you chose it :-) So we will go to Cambridge and Oxford. Oxford will be new for me as well, since I have only been there for a seminar, but not as a tourist. And Cambridge Theatre is very central, so we will go there and see "Matilda The Musical". As far as distances go, everything in London is very convenient to reach by tube (the underground in London). For dramas, you can have a look at
<br>
http://www.londontheatre.co.uk/londontheatre/whatson/drama.htm
</p>


<p>
The National Theatre is one location out of many, so you see that there are again lots of choices. Just let me know which one is most interesting for you. And of course, since you wish, we will go to Westminster Abbey. I can't remember having been inside Westminster Abbey, so that will also be new for me. So it seems that I will find out and learn a lot with you about London :-) And yes, there are lots of parks, apart from Primrose Hill, there is also Regent's Park, and Hyde Park. Moreover, close to the place you will be staying, there is Victoria Park which is also very nice. I also very much like Greenwich Park, where the prime meridian is. The Royal Observatory is also there, and if you are interested, we could go to the Planetarium where they show and explain the stars in the sky :-)
</p>


<p>
You are flying back to France tomorrow, aren't you? I wish you a safe journey, and a pleasant flight.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-11 23:31]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-11-23-31/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:18+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-11-23-31</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, August 11, 2015 5:31 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I start to wonder how could you focus on the talk when the scenery outside is so amazing and at the same time, with the boat moving back and forth :-) Anyway, the conference still sounds great.
</p>


<p>
I looked up some stuff about the places I would like to go, finally, I found that both Cambridge and Oxford are really attractive for me and hard to resist :-) So if it is possible, I prefer to go both :-) Concerning the musical, "MATILDA THE MUSICAL" seems good to me, but it will in Cambridge Theatre, I'm not sure where exactly the theatre is, will it be a little far? What's more, I would also like to try some drama, I will looked in the website of National Theatre, maybe? And then, of course, the museums, we have already talked about the British museum and the science museum, they are exactly the museums I want to visit :-) After that, yes, it should be the church, after I read "The Da Vinci Code", I really hope that I could get a chance to see Westminster Abbey, so this time the dream may comes true :-) All in all, I also find that London has many nice parks, maybe Primrose Hill is good place to have a walk? You have mentioned that you and your sister have gone to some parks, maybe you could give me some advices ;-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-11 07:17]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-11-07-17/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:17+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-11-07-17</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mardi 11 Août 2015 07:17:12
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I just arrived in London. It was a rather short, but spectacular conference, definitely the fanciest one I have experienced so far. We had a lot of talks each day, so that it was very intense as well. The very first talk was "Uffe Haagerup - In Memoriam". The speaker recalled Haagerup's life and mathematical work. It was impressive, and also moving. At the end of the talk, everyone was standing in silence to remember Haagerup... And as I said, the scenery was amazing. We were a bit unlucky with the weather, since it was almost always cloudy, but it was still fascinating. Although at some point, I was wondering whether you would really enjoy it, since when we were in the open sea, there were some waves which made the boat move back and forth quite a bit...
</p>


<p>
It is nice that you enjoyed your dinner. And it is really nice of Q to organize these seminars; you can consider yourselves lucky to have such a good advisor :-) So by now, I suppose that the seminar is finished, and that you can now enjoy a bit of free time at home, with your family. That's wonderful :-D And since you must have worked very hard the past weeks, I guess that you really need a bit of rest, so please take your time making your plans for London. There is no hurry; as long as you let me know them before you arrive, I will be able to manage, and everything will be fine :-)
</p>


<p>
Now, there are no more trips. I will just stay here in London, and wait for you, happily :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-09 22:28]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-09-22-28/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:16+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-09-22-28</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Sunday, August 9, 2015 4:28 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Thank you for your nice pictures, now I could feel what you feel, see what you see :-) This makes me feel that I'm closed to you. And you will stay in Norway until when?
</p>


<p>
Yes, the choices are increasing, but they are the happy troubles :-) But I'm sure that I will make my decision about the places and the musicals I would like to go in the next email :-) And it is very kind of you to make organizations for me, I believe we will make everything successful :-) Planing the trip is indeed part of the joy, and now I'm enjoying the happiness of it :-)
</p>


<p>
Finally, I finished my talk today, and tomorrow is the last day of our seminar, after that, I will spend the last two days in Wuhan at home, which is good :-) Today night, we had a "good-bye" dinner with the other people in our seminar, I always thought the dinner was a kind of boring but today, it was nice, Sukochev was also there, he gave a very emotional speech :-) And we students also expressed our thanks to Q for organizing this seminar where we learn a lot during this vacation.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-08-09 01:12]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-09-01-12/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:36:15+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-08-09-01-12</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Dimanche 9 Août 2015 01:12:57
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, time passed and now, we just have to wait two weeks until we meet, finally :-) And it's good that you are beginning to make some plans. This is part of the joy, isn't it? At least for me, planning a trip is fun because it makes me look forward to it even more :-) So once you have decided what you would like to see, just let me know, and I can help with the organization, and I can also try to find the most efficient routes. Well, OK, you are right, in my case it is already a success if we find the way at all ;-) Concerning musicals, my sister and I went to the musical "Beautiful", which was about the famous singer and songwriter Carole King and her (love) stories, and we went to "Songs for a New World", which was about important moments in life. There is a lot going on, for example, here are two websites showing musicals:
<br>
http://www.londontheatre.co.uk/londontheatre/whatson/musicals.htm
<br>
www.officiallondontheatre.co.uk/london-shows/musical/
<br>
and here are two websites showing classical concerts:
<br>
http://www.londonclassicalconcerts.co.uk/
<br>
http://www.classical-music.com/whats-on
</p>


<p>
Hmmm, sorry, but this increases the choices... Well, at least the good thing is that musicals or concerts are usually in the evening, when the museums are already closed, so that there is no overlap.
</p>


<p>
Yes, absolutely, I agree, sharing wonderful experiences when we discover something new is so much better than doing something alone. And I'd really like to have you here with me now, because this boat trip in Norway is really amazing. The National Theater is so beautiful, it's hard to describe in words. So I've just attached some pictures, to give you an idea :-)
</p>


<p>
It seems that you are still very busy. I wish you good luck and success with your talk tomorrow! And then, I hope you will have some free time in Wuhan :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
