<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Epitaph for One Love]]></title>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-10-03T19:14:59+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Shy]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-15 23:46]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-15-23-46/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:54+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-15-23-46</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Wednesday, July 15, 2015 5:46 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Compared with one's mind, life sometimes can be more fragile,I'm released to know that your friend has recoverd from it. And I always feel really really lucky to know you, I will treasure every moment with you in my life, it's like a gift from god...
</p>


<p>
You have read many books of Walter Scott, I'm interested in the history of Scotland, maybe I will also try to read some of his works :-) It seems that he is also famous for his poetry, have you read some? Today, it came to my mind a book I read few years ago, I think maybe you will like it, it calls The song of Nibelungs, or Nibelungenlied in German, and it is also said that The Lord Of The Rings got some inspiration from this epic poem :-)
</p>


<p>
Yes, I think the swimming pool is still there, if you don't remind me, I almost forgot it :-) Maybe I will go there this weekend. Our seminar begins today, the first talk was given by Q, it takes three hours, so maybe it is more like a course. It has been years that I haven't listend the course by him, today it really reminded me of the days three years ago when I took his "fa" in the third year, his course was always wonderful, and that was the time I decided to do a PhD with him :-) As I am not familiar with the topic we discuss, in the first two weeks, I don't need to give a talk, so I asked to take in charge of arranging the notes of every talk and typing them, I think this will help me to learn things better maybe :-)
</p>


<p>
Yesterday and the day defore yesterday, it was quite hot in Wuhan, so I barely went out :-) But today, it rained heavily suddenly, so now it feels much better. My room is quite OK, it is clean and most importantly, with air conditioner and shower bath :-) and another girl in this room is also nice :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-15 05:47]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-15-05-47/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:53+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-15-05-47</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mercredi 15 Juillet 2015 05:47:30
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, I am enjoying the conference. This morning, I gave a talk. For me, the best part of a conference is after I gave my talk. That is because then I can really enjoy talks by others to get some inspiration, and don't have to worry about my own one anymore. Talking about friends, I learned a month ago in O that a good friend of mine, with who I wrote two papers, had a heart attack. That was such a surprise for me! I was really sad, because my friend was very healthy. It came totally unexpected. But at the conference now, the same friend was already well again, and he even came to the talks. When I shook his hand, I was very glad that he recovered so quickly. Thinking about this, I feel once again that I want to embrace life and treasure everything that is important to me, which includes you...
</p>


<p>
I have already read Waverley, Rob Roy and the Bride of Lammermoor by Walter Scott. I like all these novels, but most of all, I like Rob Roy. Concerning learning how to swim, I like the joke of your friend :-) It sounds familiar, I think I heard something like this before :-D I recall that one year, we visited my grandparents in the summer. And I had the great idea to go jogging, to get some exercise. I deliberately went very early in the morning. But after running two rounds on the sports field, I felt like breathing water, my heart was beating like mad, and I simply couldn't go on. After that, I decided to go swimming, and I found a swimming pool very close to my grandparents' place :-) That was quite refreshing. I'm wondering whether that swimming pool is still there...
</p>


<p>
Yes, I know J from Orléans, he will actually visit me in September. And I hope to visit him at some point later on, because I'd like to work with him on a project. Moreover, I also know C, but not so well.
</p>


<p>
How is the weather in Wuhan? And is your room OK? So starting from tomorrow, you'll be busy. I'm sure you'll learn a lot, and wish you good luck and success with the seminar :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-14 10:01]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-14-10-01/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:52+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-14-10-01</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, July 14, 2015 4:01 AM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
How is your day tomorrow? It must be wonderful, a conference with your old friends :-)
</p>


<p>
I just went the swimming pool with friends, one of them can swim very well, so I could learn something from her, maybe I will take some courses after, perhaps in someplace near the university. I drank so many times of water in the pool that day :-) My friend joked that after drinking enough water, then I could know how to swim :-)
</p>


<p>
I have moved into the dormitory in the university yesterday, and our seminar will begin at this Wendnesday. Q sent us the main reference of our seminar few days ago, it is the note of a project in Université d'Orléans called "theoremes ergodiques pour les actions de groupes". I remember you told me that you have a colleague in Orléans, right? I haven't heard Walter Scott before, I look it up, I find he is quite famous for his historical novels of Scotland and "The Heart of Midlothian" is one of them.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-13 06:15]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-13-06-15/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:51+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-13-06-15</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Lundi 13 Juillet 2015 06:15:16
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
your achievement is well-deserved. And I think that if someone has you as a sister, that person must feel very very lucky :-)
</p>


<p>
Oh, so you are learning to swim? Are you taking courses? I still remember that you were not very comfortable when we took a boat at the East Lake in Wuhan ;-) So I think that it's courageous of you to try to overcome your fear. I'm sure you'll be fine, and wish you good luck!
</p>


<p>
Yes, some books are serious, and it requires some time and effort to digest the deeper meaning. What I like about them is that we get the opportunity to really think about what the author is saying, and that is worthwhile because it makes us realize certain things. The last book I read, Die Notizen, was like that. And I did find that many things in the book made a lot of sense. Now I've started to read Walter Scott's "The Heart of Midlothian".
</p>


<p>
Yes, that's true, it's really nice to sit together with family. I think that after I moved away from Muenster, I realized even more than before how important my family is for me. Usually, if we find the time, we like to play cards together in the evening. This time, however, my sister is rather busy, because she is taking exams soon. For me, the conference starts tomorrow. I look forward to some interesting talks, and to meeting some colleagues and old friends. It is the first time for me after I moved to London to come back to Muenster for a conference, so that is kind of special.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-12 18:22]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-12-18-22/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:50+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-12-18-22</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Sunday, July 12, 2015 12:22 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Thank you so much for your congratulations :-) In fact, you are the first person who says this to me, Q has just submitted it, and I recieved your email after that :-) And when I read that you are happy and proud, I really feel you are like a brother to me :-D Your words make me feel warm and emcouraged. Yes, I checked also, really, a coincidence I have to say, so 9 July is a special day for both of us!
</p>


<p>
Sleepless in Seattle is also one of the first romantic movies I watched, I was amazed how people can comfort each other in such a distance.I don't know You've Got Mail, I will try it some time. You watched One Hour Photo with your family? That sounds good, no matter what the movie is, sitting with your family and enjoying a beautiful time like this is already a wonderful thing to me :-)
</p>


<p>
As for Der Zauberberg, it is a huge and serious novel indeed. It is not something I can read as a pleasure and I feel that the style of auther's language is quite ironic sometimes, I wish I could tell you my deeper thoughts after I finish it :-) Yesterday I went to the swimming pool, learning to swim is really a difficult thing for me, because I have to overcome the fear to the water first :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-11 16:33]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-11-16-33/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:49+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-11-16-33</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Samedi 11 Juillet 2015 16:33:02
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yesterday, when I checked the new submissions of papers on the arXiv, I saw your joint paper with  XX and Q. I have to say: Congratulations! That is your first paper :-) I feel happy for you, and proud, too :-D Well, this marks the start of your journey through mathematics, and I wish you success and luck on your way! I really want to toast you in celebration. Let's do that when you are in London :-D Afterwards, I thought back how it was for me. So I checked and found out that my first paper was submitted to arXiv on exactly the same day, 9 July, seven years ago! What a coincidence :-)
</p>


<p>
You know quite a few movies, and very nice ones! In particular, I like Sleepless in Seattle. That was one of the first romantic movies I watched, and I was really moved. It gave me a sense how deep feelings can be. Later on, there was another romantic movie with the same actors, Tom Hanks and Meg Ryan, it's called You've Got Mail. I also liked that one a lot :-)
</p>


<p>
I arrived home yesterday. It's nice to be with my family. And it's good to know that you enjoy your time at home as well. We watched this movie One Hour Photo. Robin Williams' acting is again very impressive. But the character he plays is a very sad one, so I'm not sure that I would really recommend the movie... And yes, Thomas Mann is a famous writer. Unfortunately, I haven't read Der Zauberberg. I did read the book Der Untertan by this brother, Heinrich Mann, but that was quite some time ago. I'm curious to hear your opinion, whether you recommend Der Zauberberg.
</p>


<p>
You know, many people, especially girls, would love to have your "problem" of being "too thin" :-D When I was very small, my parents and grandparents gave me a lot to eat, they fed me so well that I got strong. But then my mother thought that I was too heavy, and told me to eat less. And in recent years, she thinks that I am thin, and wants me to eat more. So I can never do it right :-) What I learned from this is that what really matters is that we ourselves are happy and comfortable the way we are, and that we don't have to worry about things like weight too much, because the people we care about will like us anyway...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-10 15:05]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-10-15-05/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:48+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-10-15-05</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Friday, July 10, 2015 9:05 AM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Oh, you also like Robin Williams? Yes, I watched Good Will Hunting few years ago, the psychologist he played is very impressive. I don't know One Hour Photo, I search some information about it, it seems to be a nice movie ;-) As for Tom Hanks, he also played in so many good movies, Forrest Gump of course, and there are many others I like very much, for example, Sleepless in Seattle, Saving Private Ryan, The termial and Cloud Atlas :-)
</p>


<p>
I am happy to read that you make good progress on your paper and you spend a good time in Holland. And my day at home is very nice except for the jetlag problem :-) The night of the day I wrote the last letter to you, I was sleepless the whole night, maybe just because I got too much sleep before that :-) But now it becomes normal. My mother also cooks very well everytime I go home, and I hope that I could gain some weight after this like you because I'm too thin :-) Moreover, the weather in Wuhan is not too hot this week, so it is better than I expected ;-) Yesterday I began to read Der Zauberberg by Thomas Mann, I'm sure Thomas Mann is quite famous in Germany, do you know this novel?
</p>


<p>
Oh, your old high school seems very amazing to me, expecially it is run by a Bishop, so it must be a special school. You know, in the 民国, there are also many high school like this in China, many great writers in that period went to these schools and in their works, there are also many descriptions about this, so I really hope I could see it oneday :-D
</p>


<p>
I have contacted one of the girls in our deparment, she agreed to offer me a place in her dormitory, which is the newest in the university, so I think the condition will be better this time :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-09 19:26]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-09-19-26/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:47+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-09-19-26</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Jeudi 9 Juillet 2015 19:26:42
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I like the view you described. I am also often amazed by it when I am flying above the clouds. Also, the clouds themselves look very nice, fluffy, like cotton wool, as though it would be very comfortable lying on them :-) And what a funny coincidence, maybe you can tell me more about the movie when we visit the British museum :-D Robin Williams played quite a few interesting characters, I remember him in Good Will Hunting, do you know the movie? I also saw him in Mrs. Doubtfire and Patch Adams, and I have bought One Hour Photo as a DVD and will watch it at some point. I like his acting. Another actor I like very much is Tom Hanks, the one who played the main character in Forrest Gump.
</p>


<p>
I'm in Holland now. It's a bit funny to come here after reading the book I told you about, but I guess that some things in the book were prejudices. My host here is actually very nice, he took me to his home, where he and his family live. They have a beautiful old house with a little garden. We are working together on a joint paper and seem to make good progress.
</p>


<p>
Wow, now I really want to take you to our house, just to see whether you like the smell :-D I hope you do like it. Our house is a bit outside of the city, about 20 minutes by bus. The advantages is that the surroundings are nice, it is quiet and green, you can see some fields looking out of our windows. I think it would be really nice if you could visit us one day. Then I could also show you my old high school. It is kind of special, because it is run by the Bishop, and there is a monastery at the same place, where you can still meet nuns. The school used to be only for girls, but they opened it for boys some time ago. When I signed up for the school, it was really complicated. Because I am not Catholic, my father had to discuss with the headmaster; it was really serious. But my parents really wanted me to go there, because several of my friends went there, the school is close to where we live, and it is situated in the middle of a forest, with very nice and quiet surroundings. Looking back, I am really grateful that I went there, because it was at that school where I found my passion for mathematics :-)
</p>


<p>
Are you enjoying your time at home? Are you recovering well from the jetlag? And did you find a place to stay at the university?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-08 18:44]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-08-18-44/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:46+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-08-18-44</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Wednesday, July 8, 2015 12:44 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I must have been so tired, I told you that I slept all the afternoon yesterday, and I went to bed very early last night and when I waked up this morning(it was no longer morning in fact :-D), I found out that my mother had cooked the lunch already. And just after lunch, I got tired again so I slept for another three hours, now I'm feeling like sleeping for centuries ;-) I also dreamt of you :-)
</p>


<p>
Last Sunday, the day before I left B, it was hot in the afternoon, but then it began raining very heavily than even the hail! So it really cooled me down. I think it as a way to say bon voyage to me, I really like it, just as the way you say it to me :-)
</p>


<p>
Apart from the waiting during the flight, everything is fine, I saw the sunrise from the plane, it was a really different feeling when you see it above the cloud, sometime before the sun goes out, the different colors of sky is really beautiful, part of it is red and orange, and the other part is blue and they mixed with each other at some point. Speaking of movies, I watched the third installment of "The night at the museum", I watched the first part when I was in high school, and I don't know that they have made the third already. The first film itself is just a comedy, about all the things in American Museum of Natural History were brought back to life because a tablet from ancient Eygpt and something funny happend. What makes me think the third installment is special is that this story happens at the British museum where I'm going to visit :-) and another reason is that this is the last film of Robin Williams(The teacher in the "Dead poet society").
</p>


<p>
I suppose that you have already arrived at Holland, I hope that everything works out according to schedule :-)
</p>


<p>
You like the smell of your house? I'm starting to imagine what it will be like in summer :-) As you talk about the smell, I also want to say something about it, I think myself quite sensitive and obsessed to the smell, sometimes I might forget someone's or someplace's names but I can remember their smell :-) This feeling is quite special, everytime I come across the smell I'm familier with, it will bring back some memories.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-07 23:07]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-23-07/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:45+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-23-07</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mardi 7 Juillet 2015 23:07:15
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
sorry for interrupting you :-) It did feel a bit strange, because you didn't sign. But I thought that you were just too tired, maybe you even fell asleep in front of your computer ;-) So I'll wait for the rest of your email then.
</p>


<p>
Yes, I'm also in shock. And I feel exactly the same way as you, I want to embrace life and all that is important and precious to me; and I feel such a strong desire to be with you... But I'll say no more for now, because I have to be patient, and wait for the rest of your email :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-07 21:31]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-21-31/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:44+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-21-31</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, July 7, 2015 3:31 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Oh, I don't even know that I had sent you the email already, since I haven't finished yet :-) It must be a mistake. Yes, as soon as I got home, I spent all the afternoon sleeping. Then I got up and intended to complete my email, and I find out you have already recieved it :-)(Maybe I will finished it next time). But at the same time when I check my emailbox, I recieve a horrible news from Copenhagen that Haagerup passed away on Sunday, the fifth of July, in a drowning accident! After the huge shock, I realise the inconstancy of life, sometimes we can do nothing about it, so just cherishing what we have now...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-07 19:11]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-19-11/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:43+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-19-11</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mardi 7 Juillet 2015 19:11:29
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
oh, I am sorry to hear about the delay and all the trouble! It seems that both of us have not been lucky with flights recently. So how long was your journey in total? You must have been very very tired after that. Hopefully, you got a good rest afterwards :-) At least, after all, you arrived safely. That is the most important thing, and I am glad to know that. Sometimes we do not think about it too much, but after a long journey, just arriving safely is already a reason to be happy :-) And was the flight itself OK? Did you sleep, or where there interesting movies?
</p>


<p>
I'll go to Holland tomorrow morning. Let's hope that everything works out according to schedule :-D And Friday, I'll go back home. Going home is always connected with happy feelings and memories for me, the familiar places, the house where I grew up, ... I even like the smell of our house, especially in summer. And then, of course, being with family is nice. My mother always cooks so well when I am back, that I gain some weight every time I go home :-) So starting from this Friday, we'll both enjoy staying at home, at Hotel Mama :-D
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-07 08:27]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-08-27/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:42+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-08-27</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, July 7, 2015 2:27 AM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I missed the corresponding flight from Beijing to Wuhan again this time :-( Although I remembered my luggage :-) This trip is much much longer than I expected. First, due to some technical problems, the capital of the first flight required the reexamination of the plane before the departure, so I waited in airport for another two hour for this, which resulted in the huge delay. Then I had to change corresponding ticket which was three and half an hour later than the previous one, so another three hours' waiting, this was extremely long especially after the circumstance that I already had a long flight...
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-05 21:02]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-05-21-02/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:41+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-05-21-02</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Sun, 05 Jul 2015 21:02:38 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
you know, Friday night, after we skyped, I have dreamt of you :-) When I am with you, I have this nice and comfortable feeling, with you, I can just be myself. And in my dream, I had exactly the same feeling. I was so happy that I didn't want to wake up :-)
</p>


<p>
The tournament was OK, not too bad. I didn't have high expectations, because in these past two months, I have been traveling a lot. So I couldn't practice as often as I normally do, which means that I am currently not in best shape. All in all, I won five matches and lost four. Now I know what I want to improve and what I should focus on in my practice, which is good. The only problem is that my muscles will be aching tomorrow :-(
</p>


<p>
Germans also like to sunbath. I remember once I was in Miami, at the beach, and since I had been walking around under the sun for a few days already, I got a bit of a sunburn. So I stayed in the shadow. There was a group of Germans next to me, and I heard them saying to each other in German, without knowing that I can understand: "Why is this guy sitting in the shadow?" I think part of the reason is that a brown skin is fashionable, maybe because only rich people can afford to take holidays in the south regularly.
</p>


<p>
Have a good trip tomorrow, and enjoy your first week of holidays at home in Wuhan!
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-04 23:01]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-04-23-01/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:40+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-04-23-01</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Saturday, July 4, 2015 11:01 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I finished packing today, I told you yesterday that I won't take too much stuff, but my suitcase is still all filled and it is really heavy for me :-) How is the tournament today (and tomorrow :-)) ?
</p>


<p>
Today afternoon, I went to my office to put my desk there in order and to take the documents and books I need in the summer, on the way to my office, I could really feel that I would be melted by the sun, but in this time, I found a girl lying on the grasses and enjoyed the sunbathing there! That is crazy for me, but it seems that quite a few french people enjoy this too...
</p>


<p>
Writing to you, I'm sitting on the chair in the balcony, enjoying this godgiven coolness and quietness in the night :-D
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-02 18:34]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-02-18-34/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:39+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-02-18-34</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Thu, 02 Jul 2015 18:34:25 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
thanks for your reply. Friday evening is fine. Would you like to call me on Skype at around 20:30 B time?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-02 14:52]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-02-14-52/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:38+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-02-14-52</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Thursday, July 2, 2015 2:52 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Ah, you will paly a tournament this weekend, it's nice :-) How about the Friday? Maybe sometime after dinner?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-02 14:39]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-02-14-39/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:37+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-02-14-39</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Jeudi 2 Juillet 2015 14:39:09
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
sorry, but regarding our skype time, I just realized that Saturday morning is not convenient for me anymore. The reason is that I am playing a table tennis tournament, and it was supposed to start on Saturday afternoon. But now, they changed the starting time to Saturday morning. So I'll be playing this tournament on Saturday morning and Sunday morning. On both days, I should be free anytime after 16:00 London time (17:00 B time). If you'd be available at some point then, please let me know.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-01 23:09]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-01-23-09/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:36+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-01-23-09</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: X L
<br>
Sent: Wednesday, July 1, 2015 11:09 PM
<br>
To: r.x@e.fr
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, this Saturday at 9:30am B time is very good for me. So I'll wait for your call then.
</p>


<p>
You are too polite; the booking was no problem at all, and it was a pleasure to do it :-) It's good that we have sorted out all the organizational things now. And I also spotted the mistake with your family name instantly. Sorry about that! Strangely, in the first message they sent me about the booking, your name was correct, and your email address is also correct :-/ Well, as you told me, there have been misspellings of your name which were much worse ;-)
</p>


<p>
Oh, so you, too, have been moving. And your move was much more serious than mine. You must have been very busy. I hope it was not too exhausting, especially with this kind of weather :-( But two days is very efficient. When I had to move, it always took me ages. There are always these little belongings which I didn't even know that I possessed, and each of them reminded me of their little stories ... I hope that your new place is nice. For me, the situation at work is currently a mess. I don't even have an office right now, because they moved my stuff out, but have not yet managed to set up my new office :-(
</p>


<p>
Talking about leaving things behind, I can totally understand your feelings. But this process also makes us realize what is really important, as we often only really appreciate things if they are not there anymore ...
</p>


<p>
It's also quite hot in London. Hopefully it will rain tomorrow. I think the highest temperature I experienced was when I was attending a conference in Texas, in summer. That place was basically in a desert, with temperatures way above 40 degrees. I could really feel the sun on my skin. But it was dry, and even windy sometimes. So it doesn't really compare to summer in Wuhan. The humidity! I experienced that once. And I have to say, if it's just about the weather, I wouldn't want to be in your place starting from next week :-b But, I know, you're there for the seminar, where you'll learn a lot, so from that point of view, it will be worth it.
</p>


<p>
Writing to you, I am watching the moon right now. Tonight, it is very beautiful, big and bright; I can even see the landscape on it. I wonder how many people are watching the moon at this moment, and how many people have watched it ever since! No wonder in the book I'm reading now, the author writes that we humans know the landscape on the moon better than any place on earth ...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-30 21:52]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-30-21-52/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:35+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-30-21-52</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, June 30, 2015 9:52 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I receive the confirmation of the accommodation today, thank you so much for your help! But it seems that they had mistaken my family name :-)
</p>


<p>
It takes me two days to move out the building I lived, yesterday and today, because that building needs to be reconstructed during the summer vacantion. Only the time I do this moving can I realise how much stuff I have! My father always complains that I get too much stuff, now I could understand him better :-) Talking about your experience of moving, or more general, the changes. Sometimes I am afraid of change, yes, of course, many changes mean new opportunities, but still, sometimes it means that we have to say goodbye to the past, to the things that we are familiar with or that we cherish. Maybe keeping some old stuff with me is good way for me that I can tell myself at least something remains there.
</p>


<p>
It becomes really hot this week in B, it reaches 35 degrees today and it will be 39 degrees in this weekend! This is very abnormal in B. Other guys in our office comforted me that it will become normal next week, but I told them that I will be in Wuhan next week, and it's much hotter than here :-)
</p>


<p>
If you get the time, maybe we can skype in the morning of this Saturday? Around 9:30?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
