<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Epitaph for One Love]]></title>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-10-03T10:44:44+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Shy]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-25 00:18]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-25-00-18/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:30+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-25-00-18</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Thu, 25 Jun 2015 00:18:04 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
in our hearts and in our thoughts, we will always be together, forever. And compared to infinity, two months does not feel that long... But you are right, having things to do helps a lot. For me, last week passed away quickly, because I had a conference. And I'm sure that once you are in China, time will pass faster for you. Thinking about it, I find myself in a paradoxical situation. On the one hand, when I think about you, I just feel a strong desire to meet you again, and time does not pass at all. On the other hand, the thought of you gives me motivation and energy to work really, really hard, and when I am completely absorbed in my work, then time does pass faster. So, in total, does time pass more quickly or more slowly?
</p>


<p>
Oh yes, that experience you are describing is an absolute classic, I think that every mathematician goes through these situations many many times. I remember once when I was doing my PhD, I thought I had a brilliant idea, which would solve a main problem of my thesis. So I made an appointment with my advisor the next morning. But later in the evening, when I thought about it again, my argument fell apart. So the meeting the next day was very embarrassing. Fortunately, my advisor was sympathetic and not angry with me :-) Some time after that, I did manage to solve the problem. And you can imagine that I checked everything many many times :-D Although these failures seem to lead nowhere, I think that they are actually quite important. We can learn a lot and gain some insights, in particular if we understand what exactly went wrong, and why.
</p>


<p>
I came back yesterday night. It was a short conference, and for me, it was even shorter than expected: My plan was to take a flight to Aberdeen arriving around lunchtime. However, at the airport they told me that my flight was canceled. There was even no explanation why. So they put me in a flight to Edinburgh, and I had to go by train to Aberdeen, which took another three hours or so. In the end, I arrived around dinnertime. Fortunately, my talk was the next morning. At first, I was really annoyed. But at some point, I told myself that there is nothing I could do, so I just relaxed and took it easy. And actually, the train ride from Edinburgh to Aberdeen is very nice, most of it is along the coast, with a view of the sea. So at least not everything was bad.
</p>


<p>
Oh, you're right, I didn't explain the moving activity well :-) Let me try again: Currently, our offices are on one side of the building which faces the place where the new building will be built. While they are constructing the new building, they also have to work on that part of the old building, maybe to connect the two. Besides, since our old offices are close to the construction site, it would be very noisy. That is why we have to move to another part of the old maths building. Once the new building is finished, we move there, and they work on the remaining part of the old maths building. So when you visit me, the maths department will be a complete mess. But I suppose we are not going to spend that much time in my office anyway ;-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-23 19:27]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-23-19-27/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:29+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-23-19-27</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, June 23, 2015 7:27 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I can totally understand your excitement, because I feel exactly the same as you :-) But from now, it seems that two months is really a longtime, maybe it's better to keep myself busy so that the time will pass faster (at least I hope so). Yes, "forever" is a beautiful word for me, it is a word with strong emotion and I also find a similar word in mathematics, which is the symbol of "infinity" :-) I like this symbol very much, and some times ago, I found out that a girl in our office has the tattoo of this symbol, I got excited and told her I also like it.
</p>


<p>
Yesterday afternoon I thought I might have solved the problem of the main theorem I'm working on, I got so happy, but I checked it last night, it turned out I had made a huge mistake, so now, I have to start all over again :-) Will you do back tonight? And how is it?
</p>


<p>
I'm sorry, but I didn't get it, why you need to move out when another building is started to be built :-) A maths building with a roofgarden? That must be wonderful. And I don't know that Black Forest cake is that sweet, maybe just because the cake I tasted is not authentic enough :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-21 14:57]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-21-14-57/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:28+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-21-14-57</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Dimanche 21 Juin 2015 14:57:10
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
this is wonderful news indeed! When I read that you got your visa, I could feel my heart beating faster than usual, so big is my excitement! I'm relieved that everything worked out. Well done :-) A look at the calendar tells me that there two months left now. So time does pass, slowly, but steadily. And then, we'll meet again! I feel such a desire to see you, it is hard to describe in words, the feeling is so strong...
</p>


<p>
I recently came across a song by The Beach Boys called "Forever", and I immediately liked it. Maybe it's mainly because of the lyrics, they start like this "If every word I said Could make you laugh I'd talk forever I ask the sky just what we had It shone forever If the song I sing to you Could fill your heart with joy I'd sing forever ..."
</p>


<p>
My first time in O was in 2009, so seven years ago. There were two years with two meetings. Some time ago, a colleague celebrated his first birthday in O, he has spent more than 52 weeks there! Yes, Black Forest cake is famous for that region, and it's very popular. I also like it, but it's very sweet, maybe a bit too much if I'm honest :-)
</p>


<p>
Next month, they start to build our new maths building. It will be next to the old one. Once the new building is finished, they will renovate the old one. So next week, we have to move. The whole construction is supposed to take two years, but people already gossip that it will take much longer. Hopefully, it won't be too noisy. It will definitely bring some inconveniences, for instance, I will have to temporarily share an office with a colleague. But the new building is supposed to be very nice, it will even have a roofgarden :-)
</p>


<p>
Yes, it is better to teach less so that you can concentrate on the quality of your teaching. I think it will be a very interesting and helpful experience. As always, every challenge helps you to develop and improve. And I'm sure that you will try your best :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-20 13:28]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-20-13-28/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:27+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-20-13-28</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Saturday, June 20, 2015 1:28 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I like your explain that it is a way how rain loves me back :-) 9th time, which means nine years? That's a longtime really. I also saw your photos there, but you seem to haven't changed a bit, always the same smile:-) Today, it comes to my mind that there is a kind of cake called "Black Forest" which I like very much, I guess maybe it comes from Black Forest where gives its name?
</p>


<p>
I'm so excited that I received my passport and Visa yesterday afternoon, and I want to tell you this good news as soon as I can, so now I will say, see you in London!
</p>


<p>
Yesterday, I talked to the person in charge of teaching, finally, he decided to let me give the course of mathematiques for students who are not in our departement, maybe in biology. It takes just 38 hours, which is less heavy. But in fact, in some sense, we both think it is more difficult to explain the math for those who don't do math, which requires more language abilities, anyway, he gave me a chance to have a try, and I will do my best, so there are lots of things to prepare this summer...But after the summer, I will have a wonderful trip to London with you, it's really good to have something to look forward :-D
</p>


<p>
Best wishes, and have a nice weekend,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-20 01:13]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-20-01-13/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:26+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-20-01-13</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Samedi 20 Juin 2015 01:13:25
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
your story with the rain made me smile and feel sorry at the same time. I had to smile because of the irony of the situation. Maybe it was because the rain read the part of your email where you expressed your love, and decided to love you back, in its own way ;-) But then, more seriously, I hope that you didn't have a long way to go. At least you were home afterwards and could get dry and warm. It would be worse if the rain would have caught you on your way somewhere else. Actually, it rained quite a bit in O this week. The view was very nice, because we were in the mountains, so that the clouds were very low and the forest was covered by mist. When a colleague said to me that the rain is nice to watch, I thought to myself: "Yes, as long as we are indoor and dry." As though I knew your story already...
</p>


<p>
I also had an experience with rain. At some point last year, I went back to Muenster just for a few days. And exactly on one of these days, it rained heavily. Really heavily. I had never seen something like this before. It was even in the German news. Afterwards, our basement was under water, not much, but it took us one day to get the water out of it, and it took weeks to dry. Later on, we found out that other people had much bigger problems, so that we were rather lucky.
</p>


<p>
Back to O: I checked, and found out that this week was my 9th time in O. I hadn't realize myself. In the O photo collection, there are even some photos of me, as an individual :-) And yes, it is really helpful to read some talks, or to see some slides. For example, these things help a lot if we want to get an overview, or if we want to understand motivations or central ideas.
</p>


<p>
I just arrived in London. Next Monday, I have another conference in Aberdeen (Scotland). It's a bit too much, but the conference is only for two days, and after that, things get more quiet, which is good.
</p>


<p>
Did you find a good solution for your teaching next semester?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-18 22:54]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-18-22-54/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:25+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-18-22-54</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Thursday, June 18, 2015 10:54 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I saw the homepage today, there are many informations about its library, I saw the picture, at first, I thought it was a comprehensive library with all kinds of books, then I realized it is just for mathematics! No wonder it is famous, it is really big! I also found a list of all the talks in the recent years, and then I found a talk given by Junge in 2013 in this workshop about the pseudo-differential operator is quite interesting, it's like a windfalls :-) There are photos of the participants every two years, so I understand why you said that you kind of grow up there :-)
</p>


<p>
Yes, it still rains, but it's quite tragic today. It has been sunny all the day yesterday and today morning, so I didn't take my umbrella to the office today, but when I was about to leave the office before dinner, it began to rain very heavily... It was already late, there no one else in our office, so I stayed there for another half an hour waiting for the rain to stop, but it never stopped, finally I had to walk home in the heavy rain... It's really funny for me that I just said I love the rain, and it puts me in this situation today :-)
</p>


<p>
I have already bought the ticket to China, I will leave on 6 July and go back on 13 August. Yes, we had the meeting yesterday, but I will still meet the responsible person of teaching tomorrow since I find the teaching task is too much for me, there will be three classes every week, and I have no experience before, so it might take too much time to prepare and I'm not sure I can do it well. Anyway, we will try to find a solution tomorrow.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-18 00:01]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-18-00-01/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:24+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-18-00-01</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Thu, 18 Jun 2015 00:01:23 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
thank you for giving me this wonderful picture, how you enjoy the rain, listening to the raindrops, feeling comfortable, quiet and peaceful... Is it still raining? I also feel that rain has something refreshing and cleaning, and apart from practical issues like when I have to cycle through rain, I enjoy it a lot, the sound of raindrops on the window, and especially the moment just after the rain, which is very clean and clear. But at the same time, if it has been rainy or cloudy for several days in a row, I am actually quite happy to see the sun. Weather has a big influence on our mood, hasn't it?
</p>


<p>
O is a wonderful place; for me, it's unique. I told you about the surroundings, but there is also a beautiful library, people say that if you can't find something in O, then probably nowhere else. I remember someone starting his talk by saying that just sitting in the library makes him ten times smarter than usual :-) And lots of interesting people come together, usually these are the experts in the field. For instance this now is the NG workshop, which takes place every two years. The talks, the discussions, the social aspects, all this creates an atmosphere which is unique in my eyes. I gave my talk on Monday this time, and it was great to get rid of that already at the beginning. In some sense, I grew up with O, since my advisor is one of the organizers, so I was so lucky to have come here already several times. And there are some traditions, for instance, every Wednesday, we hike to a small village in the Black Forest, have a piece of cake at a local cafe, hike back, and then have a barbeque. And today is (or was) Wednesday :-D
</p>


<p>
Yes, after watching "The Imitation Game", I was also quite sad, and angry, too, seeing what Turing had to endure after the great service he did. He was actually only pardoned two years ago. His personal life was sort of tragic. And feeling regret is one of the most scary things in life. But it's probably unavoidable, just like what you wrote about our fears. All we can do is to try our best to make the right decisions, to do well what is in our hands, and to take responsibility.
</p>


<p>
By the way, I am still keeping this piece of paper you gave me with your email address in your handwriting :-)
</p>


<p>
How is your week going? Has the meeting about teaching already taken place? And have you bought your flight ticket to China?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-16 19:38]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-16-19-38/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:23+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-16-19-38</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, June 16, 2015 7:38 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Your trip to O seems wonderful to me, not to mention the amazing "Hogwarts train"! Now I can even smell the scent of grass and trees in the air there... It's lucky to be a mathematician that sometimes you can go to the lovely places for a conference, isn't it? Have you already given the speech, and how is the conference?
</p>


<p>
It has been rainy in B since Sunday, and it will rain all this week. This is quite a good news for me, it makes the weather less hot, and more importantly, I like the rain very much, yes, it makes some inconvenience sometimes, but I really enjoy the time sitting next to the window, listening the sound of rain, breathing the fresh air, and writing to you at this moment, it makes me feel the world is quite and peaceful :-)
</p>


<p>
This weekend, I watched "The Imitation Game". What Joan said to Turing when he revealed he was homosexual gave me a deep impression, they really accompanied each other in their own way, it is very sad that he never been able to get the reply from his beloving Christopher after he encrypted "I love you" in the note but still he got a friend Joan understood him very well. And at the end of the story his lonely back after he turned off the light also made me feel life is full of regrets...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-14 21:21]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-14-21-21/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:22+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-14-21-21</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Sun, 14 Jun 2015 21:21:07 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
if you were next to me now, I would ask you to pinch me, to make sure that I am not dreaming :-) You are so nice and cute! And you have a big heart. If I am able to warm it, if I can give you just a little portion of the warmth, comfort and energy you are giving me, then I'd be more than happy to do so. It's a modern fairy tale, just like Forrest Gump :-) It's good to have you, that we have each other.
</p>


<p>
I'm glad to know that the procedure was simple and quick, and let's hope your visa will come back soon. And it's also good that you can attend the meeting, since it can be helpful.
</p>


<p>
I just arrived in O, which is in the Black Forrest. The surroundings are picturesque, it's very quiet, in the mountains, in the middle of a forest, the air is fresh, you can hear birds singing... It usually takes quite some time to get there, because the place is really in the middle of nowhere. We usually go by train, and the train ride is somehow part of the experience, a bit like a school trip, and also a bit like when the students go to Hogwarts in Harry Potter :-D I'm looking forward to several talks, I think they will be interesting.
</p>


<p>
Cheesecake? Really? I also like it a lot, and so does my sister. So I can already see the three of us sitting in a nice cafe with three pieces of cheesecake ... a wonderful thought :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-13 17:11]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-13-17-11/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:21+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-13-17-11</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Saturday, June 13, 2015 5:11 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Thank you for your reply, it is so heart-warming and even about to make me cry:-) Just like what Forrest Gump said, "Life was like a box of chocolates. You never know what you're gonna get." I'm really happy that I become part of your life and that you become part of mine, then we could discover them together. Yes, you are right, age is just a number, I told you that I don't think you have got thirty because I saw a boy inside your heart, a boy likes ice cream, a boy will get nervous sometimes, a boy admires the stars in the sky of night, a boy takes our memories as treasure :-D Yesterday was quite ok, the procedure was simple, it took me just thirty minutes, and now all I can do is waiting for my visa. Since it was quicker than I expected, I got the time to drink something in a restaurant, and I found the cheesecake there :-) I like cheesecake very much, but It is not so common in France, so I was happy that I found one. And by the way, the small meeting in Friday I told you has been cancelled due to the great absences, and been moved to next week :-)
</p>


<p>
Bon weekend,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-12 09:05]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-12-09-05/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:20+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-12-09-05</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Fri, 12 Jun 2015 09:05:55 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
you are an angel :-) Thank you so much! You have given me two wonderful birthday presents: Talking to you on skype, and now your wonderful email. I really enjoyed skyping with you, it made me feel very relaxed and close to you, as though our conversations in Wuhan were just yesterday. And then your email on my birthday, I had to read it over and over again, I stopped counting how many times, your stories and feelings mean a lot to me! Afterwards, I sat in my room and recalled our first week in Wuhan, like a little boy opening his treasure box :-) And I have a lot of memories; how you were surprised that I can talk Mandarin; that the hotel wanted to charge my credit card and how you saved me; how you told me that you like romantic movies, movies with feelings, and that one of your favourite movies is Dead Poets Society; that you asked about ice cream at the restaurant where we had lunch, just because you learned two days ago that I like ice cream; how we looked at each other at boring dinner tables and both had to smile... I could continue this list, it would take me forever :-) By the end of the week, we already developed a deep understanding, so that one look was enough to know what the other one was thinking. Deep down in my heart, I had the feeling that you were special, that we have many many things in common. And in the past month, writing to each other, this initial feeling indeed proved to be true, we discovered that we do share the same feelings, similar hopes and fears, like soulmates. It is wonderful to find someone like you! I guess that's why we have to trust our hearts. Like you, I always enjoy writing to you and reading your emails, sharing little pieces of our lives, it's always interesting and exciting, never boring or trivial :-D It makes us get to know each other better and better. There is a German saying: "Geteilte Freude ist doppelte Freude, geteiltes Leid is halbes Leid." It means that sharing happiness doubles the happiness, and sharing sorrow halves the sorrow. Thank you for sharing!
</p>


<p>
I had a wonderful day yesterday, very nice indeed. And now I am 30. 30. Thirty. It's just a number, isn't it? We are only as old as we feel. What really matters is not the age, but the things that happen in our lives, and the people we meet. I have met you. And I really feel that this does start a new chapter in my life. I can't wait to read the next pages, I'm excited to find out what they contain, what is going to happen next. Are you ready to discover all this together with me?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>


<p>
PS: Good luck in Paris! Hopefully, everything will go well.
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-11 20:52]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-11-20-52/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:19+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-11-20-52</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Thursday, June 11, 2015 8:52 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Do you spend a nice birthday with your family? I'm sure you do. I just want to say I wish the best for you and that everthing will be better and better with you :-) It's a wonderful thing to know you, this really makes me feel that life is full of wonders and unexpectedness. I still remember that I didn't expected anything special when I went to the airport last month, I even mistaken your name when I was about to make a pickup-board, since Q's mandarin is not that good, I misheard your name... I tried to google the name with a keyword London (that's all the information I got) many times, but there is nothing. And suddenly, just few hours before I went to airport, I notice your email adress in the email Q transmitted to me, then I know the reason why I can't find anything :-) Now I still keep this wrong pickup-board I made the first time, to mark this funny start :-) Ok, then continue the story, I said that I didn't expect anything special, but things seem to change when you wave to me, yes, it's quite possible that you always wave to people like that, but somehow, it gave me the feeling we have already known each other before... Then, we talked a lot of things in the following days, it's quite comfortable talking to you, and the feeling of being closed. And I'm happy we could keep in touch then by writing, this is a way totally different from talking, I really enjoy writing to you, sharing thoughts, the things we like and even everyday life, reading your reply makes me really happy and encouraged. Although we have met for just a month, but it seems like we have known each other for a long time, long enough for me to talk everything to you, sometimes even the complains about trivial things in life, I hope you won't feel bored :-) Now, I want to say thank you, thanks you for all the things happening...
</p>


<p>
Written in your last day of 29 years old (or the first day of 30, I'm not sure which version do you prefer) :-D
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-09 22:34]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-09-22-34/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:18+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-09-22-34</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mardi 9 Juin 2015 22:34:51
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I very much like what you said, that our fears and sad moments "make us cherish what we have". I couldn't say it better. There is this quote by Nelson Mandela, “I learned that courage was not the absence of fear, but the triumph over it. The brave man is not he who does not feel afraid, but he who conquers that fear.” You are right, sadness makes us value happiness even more. I'm happy that you think the same way as me :-) It's so nice to have someone with similar thoughts, to share feelings with :-)
</p>


<p>
From what I hear, high school in China must really be tough, with so much pressure, and from what you tell me, very boring. It seems like school in Germany is the other extreme, students are treated very nicely, sometimes too nicely. For instance, parents would blame teachers if their kids do not get good marks, or even if they get too much homework. In a way, it encourages kids to be lazy. Only afterwards, when they grow up, they realize that they have not worked hard enough, and regret it when it's too late... Also, kids get a lot of freedom, a lot of free time. For those who find things and activities they like, it's great, but it's also easy to lose orientation, just fooling around, not knowing what to do with life. That can also be scary. So there are good and bad sides everywhere, in every system, there is no perfect solution. I guess, it's not where we grow up that matters, what really matters is that we try to make the best out of it. And look at you, I would say you are doing very well, and I'm sure that it will only get better and better :-)
</p>


<p>
That sounds great, you will teach! Now it's your turn to inspire students :-D That's very exciting. Maybe you can tell me more about it when we skype? See, hear, and talk to you tomorrow :-D
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-09 10:56]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-09-10-56/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:17+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-09-10-56</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, June 9, 2015 10:56 AM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I also heard the news after I told you this movie, I feel sorry for it, especially after seeing what he has suffered from his mental illness and how they faced it together...
</p>


<p>
Although I'm a little afraid of the sadness that may come after watch "Amour", I sure I will do it someday, since I don't see sad as an emotion we should avoid. I still remember that in my high school, I watched a movie which has a very tragic ending, I was depressed for several days, everything seemed hopeless to me , even my friend found out there was something wrong with me, and asked me what happened :-) Now, I have to laugh when recalling this. Yes, now, I still get heartbreaking for the books I read, the movies I watched, however, I won't feel hopeless anymore, contrarily, I see it as a way to make us cherish what we have. Speaking of high school, I really don't like most of part of it. Yes, sometimes we got good moments, but most of time it seemed like everything we did is just for passing the university entrance exam (高考), and it is a exam really boring :-( We repeat the same thing everything, which now I feel like wasting of time and life. Ok, I shouldn't be so negative, like what I've just said, I really cherish the life I have now, doing the things I like :-)
</p>


<p>
Yesterday, I received the email, they told me I will teach "Analysis" next semester, it contains both lecture and seminar, so there are much to prepare I suppose. Ok, now I will say, See you tomorrow :-D
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-07 21:09]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-07-21-09/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:16+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-07-21-09</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Dimanche 7 Juin 2015 21:09:15
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
thank you for your encouraging words about teaching, that's very kind of you :-)
</p>


<p>
You don't have to watch "Amour" if you don't want to, I can perfectly understand your feelings. In my case, I watched the movie by chance, I haven't read about it before, so there was no courage involved, only naivety :-D About heartbreaking stories, do you know the Japanese writer Banana Yoshimoto? (Banana is not her real name.) I read Kitchen and Moonlight Shadow by her. These are really moving and heartbreaking. The first story still gave me the feeling of some hope, while the second one just made me sad...
</p>


<p>
Coming back to movies, I watched "A Beautiful Mind" yesterday. What can I say? I knew a bit about Nash's mathematical achievements, but I didn't know about his mental illness. I'm impressed that in spite of his sufferings, he became such a great mathematician! Or maybe the illness and his ingenuity were connected, maybe it was his illness which allowed him to do things normal people would never be able to do. Anyway, it seems like a very high price to pay. Nash must have been a special character, in positive and negative ways. I learned that he and his wife died in a car accident this month, coming home from Norway where he received the Abel Prize. Tragic, isn't it?
</p>


<p>
Yes, that's great, you can call me via Skype on Wednesday, at 20:00 local time in France (which is 19:00 London time). It's a good time for me. So I'll just wait for you, and make sure that I'm online and logged into Skype.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-06 18:19]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-06-18-19/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:15+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-06-18-19</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Saturday, June 6, 2015 6:19 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Thank you for your stories, the negative one and the positive one. Reading about that you just seat there and got trembling after your first lecture, it makes me laugh, since it reminds me of my same experience last year when I did my oral defense for master thesis :-) I'm sure you learned a lot from last year, asking questions is a good way to keep attention up, that's the way I expected my teacher to do when I was undergraduate. And the beauty, the importance of the proofs, that requires more understanding or admiring of what you teach, not everyone can do that, so I guess that's reason you get the positive feedback this year :-) Ah, you have got a student? I must say congratulations to you! Perhaps you can tell more about it when I call you? I'm wondering maybe I will call you in skype Wednesday night to say Gute Reise to you:-), around eight clock( in France), is that Ok for you?
</p>


<p>
In fact, I knew "Amour" because I saw a short review of someone, it writes also the main two parts in the film, the love and the pain. When facing the subject like illness and age, I always feel fragile, so I'm not sure I won't be overwhelmed by the heartbreaking seeing this film, that's the reason why I haven't watched it yet. It really needs courage :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-06 00:28]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-06-00-28/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:14+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-06-00-28</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Sat, 06 Jun 2015 00:28:02 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, absolutely, feedback is very important. If it's positive, then that's nice, but if it's negative (and honest), then we can actually learn even more. For instance, last year, my teaching was not so good. It was my first time teaching in the UK, and I was not familiar with the material of the module. So I focused on giving good lectures, explaining all the proofs in detail. For those students who paid attention, it was fine, but quite a few got bored and even started to get noisy; also, students were afraid of the proofs, especially in the exam. This year, I changed things a bit. Not the material of the module, and I also did all the proofs, but I would ask questions during my lectures to keep the attention up, and I would summarize the ideas of very long proofs. I even spent half an hour to discuss the importance, and also the beauty, of proofs. These little changes made quite a difference. I think that teaching or giving talks is a matter of practice and experience. I remember quite well the first talk I gave in our research seminar. I did a lot of preparations, and was quite nervous. And after the talk, I sat for hours in my room, my hands still trembling from the agitation :-) Thinking back, I have to laugh about myself, because in the meantime, I gave lots of talks, and feel more confident about it. So the first time may not be easy, but once you started to teach, I am sure you will get more and more confident.
</p>


<p>
Yes, I remember the scene. And I had to smile that you went to the restaurant and watched the sea. I don't think it's stupid, because that's exactly the sort of thing I can imagine myself doing :-) The only problem is that New Zealand is quite far away :-D And yes, I like "Amour". It's touching in both ways, in a nice way when you see the couple's love, but also in a heartbreaking way when you see their pain... Yes, yes, I won't say more, since you want to watch the movie :-)
</p>


<p>
If you were my PhD student, then I would be facing the following problem: On the one hand, I would want the best for you, which means that I would have to be very strict and demanding, but on the other hand, I would be afraid of making you unhappy, or that you would be angry with me. So in the end, I probably wouldn't know what to do at all ;-) More seriously, I still have to learn at lot when it comes to supervising PhD students. Actually, I just got a new student this week; we had our first meeting three days ago.
</p>


<p>
By the way, I'm going to Germany next Thursday, to visit family and for a conference. Would you like to skype before I go? I'd be available anytime you like, just let me know.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-04 21:06]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-04-21-06/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:13+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-04-21-06</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Thursday, June 4, 2015 9:06 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
It's funny, but truly sometimes if we get some feedback from others, it really encourges us, although we don't do it for rewards at the first time. And I think maybe the happiness as a teacher is to know that you really help them to do well, I'm happy to read that your students like you, perhaps it's because you do have made wonderful lectures :-) If I were few years younger, maybe I would choose you as my Ph.D. superviser :-D Hmm... Q won't be happy to hear this, haha. More seriously, I'm still not sure if I can get the chance to teach next semester, but if I get, there is still much to prepare during this summer I suppose, since I've never tried before.
</p>


<p>
"The Intouchables", in fact, I like this movie very much, but I didn't notice its music, I should have paid more attention, since now, I find them quite good. Two people who have totally different backgrounds , but they are a really perfect couple, maybe just because they both know how to respect the others. Do you remember in the end of film, the scene when the man finally meets his penfriend in a restaurant and the scenery seen from their table? The beach and the wave... They are quite impressive for me, then I found out that it is shot at the coast of Cabourg. So last year, I went to that place, found the restaurant in the movie and watched the sea from the same angle :-)It sounds a little stupide, but anyway, it's quite wonderful! Perhaps, one day, you can also experience the scenery in Lord of ring in New Zealand :-)
</p>


<p>
I heard about "Amour" before, but I haven't seen yet, since you like, I will see it.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-03 22:34]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-03-22-34/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:12+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-03-22-34</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mercredi 3 Juin 2015 22:34:07
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
awesome, that's great news! Thanks for letting me know about your bookings, and I wish you good luck in Paris, let's hope that everything will be fine. If you need to take a local train, to Reading or somewhere else, we can always buy tickets during your visit, that's easy. And yes, I also want to see you again, I want it sooo much :-) Is it really only a month since we've met in Wuhan? I really have to force myself not to think about you all the time, because that only makes the waiting time pass even more slowly :-(
</p>


<p>
I just finished checking today. Not only do we have to mark our own exams, but we also have to check the ones of our colleagues. That just means going through the scripts and making sure that the points add up correctly, and that the examiner has not overlooked something. When I said that marking is terrible, then checking is even worse. It's so boring and monotonous, you just have to turn pages and add up numbers, like a calculator. But it has to be done. Anyway, it's over now. Maybe I shouldn't be so negative, since teaching my module this year was actually quite nice. My students were pretty good, at least that was my impression. And it's very rewarding to see students do well! There was one student who shook my hand and told me that it was an honour to be taught be me, he did that twice, and every time we meet he always greets me with a big smile and waves :-D And yesterday, a group of students came to my office to thank me for the teaching :-) So, yes, if you could do a bit of teaching, I think that would be a good experience.
</p>


<p>
Just as you say, Sissel's voice is like an angel. Very beautiful. Enya's voice also is like that. I first heard Enya in "Lord of the Rings". These are epic movies. Particularly impressive is the scenery, they filmed in New Zealand. I've never been there, but that's definitely a place I'd like to go. New Zealand and Australia must simply be beautiful. Ludovico Enaudi's music appears in the movie "The Intouchables", that's a French movie about a person in a wheelchair and a guy who takes care of him. It's quite moving to see how they help each other. Talking about French movies, I recently saw "Amour", also a very touching movie about a couple who loves each other until a very old age. Do you know it?
</p>


<p>
Wonderful, that rainbow was a very nice welcoming present for you in B! And now I also have a beautiful picture in my mind, the rainbow with its bright colours, the fresh air after the rain, the rays of sunshine breaking through the clouds, ..., and you, admiring the beauty of the rainbow, trying to touch it...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-02 23:28]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-02-23-28/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:11+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-02-23-28</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, June 2, 2015 11:28 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I'm happy that I'm quite efficient tonight, I have accomplished the applying procedures on the internet and booked all the tickets I need for application. Concerning the ticket to Reading, because after I told my friend that I get a chance to meet her, she prefers maybe go somewhere else near London with me instead of Reading, and she still haven't made her mind yet. My appointment in Paris will be at next Friday, hope everything will be fine. If nothing goes wrong, I will arrive London st-Pancras at 15h30 23th August. Writing about this makes me excited again, I can't wait to see you again:-)
</p>


<p>
Yes, Sissel's voice is just like angel. Where does "should it matter" from? Humm, it's a good question...You don't know since I have made a mistake! :-):-), ok, the thing should be when I watched Titanic, the fascinating vocal during the movie made me obsessed, I looked it up, it's devoted by Sissel, so then I get many other her pieces, "should it matter" is one of my favorites. You say that you listened Ludovico Einaudi and Enya in the movies at the first time, in which one? Moreover, I'm very happy to know that you use the Canon to wake you up every day, because it is a music we both like, and that's indeed a wonderful start of a day.
</p>


<p>
Speaking of the rainbow after the rain, I still remember the experience when I saw a rainbow the first time after I arrived B. That may be the most wonderful rainbow I have ever seen, it had exactly seven colors, every one of them is so bright, and it seemed so closed, and I felt that I can even touch it by my hand! I have been to the sea for a few times, but I never got to the chance to see a sunset or sunrise. Now I have got a beautiful image in my mind, siting near the plage, waiting for sun to get it's head out, quietly...
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
