<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Epitaph for One Love]]></title>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-10-01T17:20:02+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Shy]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-11 22:04]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-22-04/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:46+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-22-04</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Lundi 11 Mai 2015 22:04:43
<br>
Objet: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
you are really nice. If you keep making me compliments like that, one day I will lose my sense of reality ;-) More seriously, I think one of the best things about being a mathematician is that you can travel around and meet interesting people. And I think that people are the biggest source of inspiration. But then, it is not easy to find others with similar ideas and points of view. With you, I had that feeling of being close, almost like brother and sister. Actually, what a wonderful thought: To have you as my second sister! I hope you do not mind that I think about you that way...
</p>


<p>
My skype username is t_x. But I am offline almost all the time, so you would have to let me know in advance if you would like to talk.
</p>


<p><p>
S? Hmmm, that is indeed funny, what a coincidence :-) Is he also doing maths? I am sure that I will like him. First, I thought that it would be great to visit you guys in B. But then thinking about it again, I realized that I would cause inconveniences; and I have already caused so many inconveniences for you last week in Wuhan that it will be difficult to pay back. Maybe it would really be better if you and S could visit me in London, so that I can be the host&hellip;
<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-11 13:08]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-13-08/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:45+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-13-08</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Monday, May 11, 2015 7:08 AM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
How generous you are! I feel really happy that I can make a friend like you and I enjoy writting to you. In fact, I have been using skype for few years, you can tell me your username that I can add you.
</p>


<p>
It will be nice if it is possible for you to pay a visit to B, it is a small but beautiful city, I can also introduce my boyfriend to you there, his name is S (has the same pronunciation as your name in Germany :-) ), I think you will also like him.
</p>


<p>
I agree with your opinion on the internet, it makes our lives more convenient, but in the meantime, it also makes us less willing to think. In the past, we communicated by letter in which we put a lot of thought, so is the email today. However, if we communicate in other ways, like "Wechat", it is less thoughtful.
</p>


<p>
Well, hope you have a good trip in Shanghai :-D.
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-11 07:34]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-07-34/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:44+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-07-34</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Lundi 11 Mai 2015 07:34:20
<br>
Objet: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
thank you so much for your email, it has put a big smile on my face and made me really happy :-D
</p>


<p>
London, Wuhan; B would be another option. In a month, I will go to a conference in O. This is in the Black Forest, near F. And I think that it is not too far from B. Moreover, I have a colleague in Orléans whom I am planning to visit at some point this year. So there are opportunities...
</p>


<p>
In the meantime, 21st century provides solutions if we want to talk although we are far away. I am thinking of Skype, or its Chinese analogue for online phone calls (I know it exists, but have forgotten the name). If you like the idea and want to give it a try, just let me know.
</p>


<p>
By the way, talking about 21st century, I was very much relieved that the internet connection here in my hotel in Shanghai is much faster than the one I had before. This makes me feel like coming back to 2015. At the same time, it is frightening to see how much we depend on the internet nowadays.
</p>


<p>
Have a nice week,
<br>
and best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-10 20:41]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-10-20-41/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:43+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-10-20-41</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Sunday, May 10, 2015 2:41 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Well, I'm glad to hear that everything goes fine:-D. I also really enjoy the time with you and I am happy you feel the same. I am sure we will find another chance to meet each other, maybe in London, maybe in Wuhan. Keep in touch~
</p>


<p>
Viele Grüße,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-10 18:21]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-10-18-21/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:42+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-10-18-21</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Dimanche 10 Mai 2015 18:21:11
<br>
Objet: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I just arrived safely in Shanghai. Everything went fine.
</p>


<p>
Let me thank you heartily for all your help in Wuhan. It has been a wonderful visit, but I especially enjoyed meeting you and talking to you. Hopefully, we will meet again soon. As I said, I would be more than happy to arrange a visit for you in London if you find the time. Let us keep in touch.
</p>


<p>
Merci beaucoup!
<br>
Amitiés,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
