<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Epitaph for One Love]]></title>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-10-03T15:09:36+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Shy]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-09 19:26]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-09-19-26/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:47+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-09-19-26</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Jeudi 9 Juillet 2015 19:26:42
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I like the view you described. I am also often amazed by it when I am flying above the clouds. Also, the clouds themselves look very nice, fluffy, like cotton wool, as though it would be very comfortable lying on them :-) And what a funny coincidence, maybe you can tell me more about the movie when we visit the British museum :-D Robin Williams played quite a few interesting characters, I remember him in Good Will Hunting, do you know the movie? I also saw him in Mrs. Doubtfire and Patch Adams, and I have bought One Hour Photo as a DVD and will watch it at some point. I like his acting. Another actor I like very much is Tom Hanks, the one who played the main character in Forrest Gump.
</p>


<p>
I'm in Holland now. It's a bit funny to come here after reading the book I told you about, but I guess that some things in the book were prejudices. My host here is actually very nice, he took me to his home, where he and his family live. They have a beautiful old house with a little garden. We are working together on a joint paper and seem to make good progress.
</p>


<p>
Wow, now I really want to take you to our house, just to see whether you like the smell :-D I hope you do like it. Our house is a bit outside of the city, about 20 minutes by bus. The advantages is that the surroundings are nice, it is quiet and green, you can see some fields looking out of our windows. I think it would be really nice if you could visit us one day. Then I could also show you my old high school. It is kind of special, because it is run by the Bishop, and there is a monastery at the same place, where you can still meet nuns. The school used to be only for girls, but they opened it for boys some time ago. When I signed up for the school, it was really complicated. Because I am not Catholic, my father had to discuss with the headmaster; it was really serious. But my parents really wanted me to go there, because several of my friends went there, the school is close to where we live, and it is situated in the middle of a forest, with very nice and quiet surroundings. Looking back, I am really grateful that I went there, because it was at that school where I found my passion for mathematics :-)
</p>


<p>
Are you enjoying your time at home? Are you recovering well from the jetlag? And did you find a place to stay at the university?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-08 18:44]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-08-18-44/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:46+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-08-18-44</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Wednesday, July 8, 2015 12:44 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I must have been so tired, I told you that I slept all the afternoon yesterday, and I went to bed very early last night and when I waked up this morning(it was no longer morning in fact :-D), I found out that my mother had cooked the lunch already. And just after lunch, I got tired again so I slept for another three hours, now I'm feeling like sleeping for centuries ;-) I also dreamt of you :-)
</p>


<p>
Last Sunday, the day before I left B, it was hot in the afternoon, but then it began raining very heavily than even the hail! So it really cooled me down. I think it as a way to say bon voyage to me, I really like it, just as the way you say it to me :-)
</p>


<p>
Apart from the waiting during the flight, everything is fine, I saw the sunrise from the plane, it was a really different feeling when you see it above the cloud, sometime before the sun goes out, the different colors of sky is really beautiful, part of it is red and orange, and the other part is blue and they mixed with each other at some point. Speaking of movies, I watched the third installment of "The night at the museum", I watched the first part when I was in high school, and I don't know that they have made the third already. The first film itself is just a comedy, about all the things in American Museum of Natural History were brought back to life because a tablet from ancient Eygpt and something funny happend. What makes me think the third installment is special is that this story happens at the British museum where I'm going to visit :-) and another reason is that this is the last film of Robin Williams(The teacher in the "Dead poet society").
</p>


<p>
I suppose that you have already arrived at Holland, I hope that everything works out according to schedule :-)
</p>


<p>
You like the smell of your house? I'm starting to imagine what it will be like in summer :-) As you talk about the smell, I also want to say something about it, I think myself quite sensitive and obsessed to the smell, sometimes I might forget someone's or someplace's names but I can remember their smell :-) This feeling is quite special, everytime I come across the smell I'm familier with, it will bring back some memories.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-07 23:07]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-23-07/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:45+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-23-07</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mardi 7 Juillet 2015 23:07:15
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
sorry for interrupting you :-) It did feel a bit strange, because you didn't sign. But I thought that you were just too tired, maybe you even fell asleep in front of your computer ;-) So I'll wait for the rest of your email then.
</p>


<p>
Yes, I'm also in shock. And I feel exactly the same way as you, I want to embrace life and all that is important and precious to me; and I feel such a strong desire to be with you... But I'll say no more for now, because I have to be patient, and wait for the rest of your email :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-07 21:31]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-21-31/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:44+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-21-31</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, July 7, 2015 3:31 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Oh, I don't even know that I had sent you the email already, since I haven't finished yet :-) It must be a mistake. Yes, as soon as I got home, I spent all the afternoon sleeping. Then I got up and intended to complete my email, and I find out you have already recieved it :-)(Maybe I will finished it next time). But at the same time when I check my emailbox, I recieve a horrible news from Copenhagen that Haagerup passed away on Sunday, the fifth of July, in a drowning accident! After the huge shock, I realise the inconstancy of life, sometimes we can do nothing about it, so just cherishing what we have now...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-07 19:11]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-19-11/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:43+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-19-11</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mardi 7 Juillet 2015 19:11:29
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
oh, I am sorry to hear about the delay and all the trouble! It seems that both of us have not been lucky with flights recently. So how long was your journey in total? You must have been very very tired after that. Hopefully, you got a good rest afterwards :-) At least, after all, you arrived safely. That is the most important thing, and I am glad to know that. Sometimes we do not think about it too much, but after a long journey, just arriving safely is already a reason to be happy :-) And was the flight itself OK? Did you sleep, or where there interesting movies?
</p>


<p>
I'll go to Holland tomorrow morning. Let's hope that everything works out according to schedule :-D And Friday, I'll go back home. Going home is always connected with happy feelings and memories for me, the familiar places, the house where I grew up, ... I even like the smell of our house, especially in summer. And then, of course, being with family is nice. My mother always cooks so well when I am back, that I gain some weight every time I go home :-) So starting from this Friday, we'll both enjoy staying at home, at Hotel Mama :-D
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-07 08:27]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-08-27/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:42+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-07-08-27</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, July 7, 2015 2:27 AM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I missed the corresponding flight from Beijing to Wuhan again this time :-( Although I remembered my luggage :-) This trip is much much longer than I expected. First, due to some technical problems, the capital of the first flight required the reexamination of the plane before the departure, so I waited in airport for another two hour for this, which resulted in the huge delay. Then I had to change corresponding ticket which was three and half an hour later than the previous one, so another three hours' waiting, this was extremely long especially after the circumstance that I already had a long flight...
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-05 21:02]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-05-21-02/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:41+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-05-21-02</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Sun, 05 Jul 2015 21:02:38 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
you know, Friday night, after we skyped, I have dreamt of you :-) When I am with you, I have this nice and comfortable feeling, with you, I can just be myself. And in my dream, I had exactly the same feeling. I was so happy that I didn't want to wake up :-)
</p>


<p>
The tournament was OK, not too bad. I didn't have high expectations, because in these past two months, I have been traveling a lot. So I couldn't practice as often as I normally do, which means that I am currently not in best shape. All in all, I won five matches and lost four. Now I know what I want to improve and what I should focus on in my practice, which is good. The only problem is that my muscles will be aching tomorrow :-(
</p>


<p>
Germans also like to sunbath. I remember once I was in Miami, at the beach, and since I had been walking around under the sun for a few days already, I got a bit of a sunburn. So I stayed in the shadow. There was a group of Germans next to me, and I heard them saying to each other in German, without knowing that I can understand: "Why is this guy sitting in the shadow?" I think part of the reason is that a brown skin is fashionable, maybe because only rich people can afford to take holidays in the south regularly.
</p>


<p>
Have a good trip tomorrow, and enjoy your first week of holidays at home in Wuhan!
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-04 23:01]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-04-23-01/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:40+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-04-23-01</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Saturday, July 4, 2015 11:01 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I finished packing today, I told you yesterday that I won't take too much stuff, but my suitcase is still all filled and it is really heavy for me :-) How is the tournament today (and tomorrow :-)) ?
</p>


<p>
Today afternoon, I went to my office to put my desk there in order and to take the documents and books I need in the summer, on the way to my office, I could really feel that I would be melted by the sun, but in this time, I found a girl lying on the grasses and enjoyed the sunbathing there! That is crazy for me, but it seems that quite a few french people enjoy this too...
</p>


<p>
Writing to you, I'm sitting on the chair in the balcony, enjoying this godgiven coolness and quietness in the night :-D
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-02 18:34]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-02-18-34/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:39+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-02-18-34</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Thu, 02 Jul 2015 18:34:25 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
thanks for your reply. Friday evening is fine. Would you like to call me on Skype at around 20:30 B time?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-02 14:52]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-02-14-52/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:38+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-02-14-52</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Thursday, July 2, 2015 2:52 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Ah, you will paly a tournament this weekend, it's nice :-) How about the Friday? Maybe sometime after dinner?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-02 14:39]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-02-14-39/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:37+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-02-14-39</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Jeudi 2 Juillet 2015 14:39:09
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
sorry, but regarding our skype time, I just realized that Saturday morning is not convenient for me anymore. The reason is that I am playing a table tennis tournament, and it was supposed to start on Saturday afternoon. But now, they changed the starting time to Saturday morning. So I'll be playing this tournament on Saturday morning and Sunday morning. On both days, I should be free anytime after 16:00 London time (17:00 B time). If you'd be available at some point then, please let me know.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-07-01 23:09]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-01-23-09/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:36+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-07-01-23-09</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: X L
<br>
Sent: Wednesday, July 1, 2015 11:09 PM
<br>
To: r.x@e.fr
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, this Saturday at 9:30am B time is very good for me. So I'll wait for your call then.
</p>


<p>
You are too polite; the booking was no problem at all, and it was a pleasure to do it :-) It's good that we have sorted out all the organizational things now. And I also spotted the mistake with your family name instantly. Sorry about that! Strangely, in the first message they sent me about the booking, your name was correct, and your email address is also correct :-/ Well, as you told me, there have been misspellings of your name which were much worse ;-)
</p>


<p>
Oh, so you, too, have been moving. And your move was much more serious than mine. You must have been very busy. I hope it was not too exhausting, especially with this kind of weather :-( But two days is very efficient. When I had to move, it always took me ages. There are always these little belongings which I didn't even know that I possessed, and each of them reminded me of their little stories ... I hope that your new place is nice. For me, the situation at work is currently a mess. I don't even have an office right now, because they moved my stuff out, but have not yet managed to set up my new office :-(
</p>


<p>
Talking about leaving things behind, I can totally understand your feelings. But this process also makes us realize what is really important, as we often only really appreciate things if they are not there anymore ...
</p>


<p>
It's also quite hot in London. Hopefully it will rain tomorrow. I think the highest temperature I experienced was when I was attending a conference in Texas, in summer. That place was basically in a desert, with temperatures way above 40 degrees. I could really feel the sun on my skin. But it was dry, and even windy sometimes. So it doesn't really compare to summer in Wuhan. The humidity! I experienced that once. And I have to say, if it's just about the weather, I wouldn't want to be in your place starting from next week :-b But, I know, you're there for the seminar, where you'll learn a lot, so from that point of view, it will be worth it.
</p>


<p>
Writing to you, I am watching the moon right now. Tonight, it is very beautiful, big and bright; I can even see the landscape on it. I wonder how many people are watching the moon at this moment, and how many people have watched it ever since! No wonder in the book I'm reading now, the author writes that we humans know the landscape on the moon better than any place on earth ...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-30 21:52]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-30-21-52/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:35+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-30-21-52</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, June 30, 2015 9:52 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I receive the confirmation of the accommodation today, thank you so much for your help! But it seems that they had mistaken my family name :-)
</p>


<p>
It takes me two days to move out the building I lived, yesterday and today, because that building needs to be reconstructed during the summer vacantion. Only the time I do this moving can I realise how much stuff I have! My father always complains that I get too much stuff, now I could understand him better :-) Talking about your experience of moving, or more general, the changes. Sometimes I am afraid of change, yes, of course, many changes mean new opportunities, but still, sometimes it means that we have to say goodbye to the past, to the things that we are familiar with or that we cherish. Maybe keeping some old stuff with me is good way for me that I can tell myself at least something remains there.
</p>


<p>
It becomes really hot this week in B, it reaches 35 degrees today and it will be 39 degrees in this weekend! This is very abnormal in B. Other guys in our office comforted me that it will become normal next week, but I told them that I will be in Wuhan next week, and it's much hotter than here :-)
</p>


<p>
If you get the time, maybe we can skype in the morning of this Saturday? Around 9:30?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-29 00:12]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-29-00-12/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:34+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-29-00-12</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Lundi 29 Juin 2015 00:12:33
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, I brought all this stuff to London, into my apartment :-D It was not only because I like my things, but there were actually practical reasons. One was that my new University in London agreed to pay for the moving expenses. And since I had lots of stuff (mostly books) anyway, I just asked a moving company with a really big car to transport some furniture as well. The other reason is that I have put all my furniture into the basement of my parents' house. But because I had quite a bit of stuff, our basement is really full. My mother joked that it looks like we are opening a furniture store :-) So I thought, it might be a good idea to at least bring a little bit of furniture with me.
</p>


<p>
Talking about moving, we moved quite a lot when I was small. And I didn't like it, because it meant saying farewell to friends, to familiar places. I remember once before one of our moves, I was looking out from our window and thinking to myself that this view is going to disappear, like all the previous ones, and it made me sad. Only when we came to Muenster did our moving activities stop. Maybe that's why I stayed in Muenster for such a long time :-) In academics, especially at the beginning of a career, it is very common to move around often. But this is a bit different, because I understand now that new environments also mean new chances. Still, for me, the idea of settling down at some place one day seems attractive.
</p>


<p>
S University is a very good place, no? From what I hear, apart from a good thesis, finding a postdoc position relies a lot on personal contacts and references. The subject matters as well, but I know quite a few colleagues who are happy to take postdocs working on slightly different, but related areas. And I also know several people who used the transition period from PhD to postdoc to go into new directions in research, starting their own journey through mathematics. So I guess apart from working on one's thesis, it is important to develop broad interests. In my case, after my PhD, my supervisor kept me as a postdoc. On the one hand, this spared me some trouble, on the other hand, I am missing this experience. But I can see the perspective of colleagues, who sometimes have open positions and desperately try to find good candidates. So there will be chances.
</p>


<p>
I listened to Les Petits Chanteurs de Saint Marc. Their singing is really beautiful. Their voices are so soft and tender. Like angels.
</p>


<p>
Tomorrow in a week, you are going back to China, aren't you? I'm thinking that maybe, if you are not too busy, we could skype at the end of next week so that I can wish you 'Bon voyage' :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-27 23:00]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-27-23-00/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:33+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-27-23-00</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Saturday, June 27, 2015 11:00 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Oh, you brought your desk, bookshelf and even your chair from Germany? That must be a really long journey for them :-D That's funny. They are still in your apartment in London now? In fact, before I went to university, I also enjoy more the study time at home, sitting alone before my desk and bookshelf really made me more concentrated and relaxed, you know that the high schools in China have always dozens of homeworks to do, many of my classmates can do most of them at school, but I just can't, I preferred to do at home after school, which made me end in sleeping very late every night :-( But after I came to university, I had to live with other girls in the dormitory, at first, I really could not get used to it, but when I can't change the environment, I have to change myself, so everything is fine now ;-)
</p>


<p>
That students is two years senior than me, so I won't be the most senior students after he leaves. I happy to say this, because this means that I'm still not too old :-) More seriously, he mainly works on the Sobolev spaces on qt, so I could ask him at lot of questions. But there is also a problem, there are not many people work on this area now, so it is not easy to find a post-doc, he haven't got a confirmed reply yet, but it is possible that he will go to S University and do post-doc with H L.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-26 23:54]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-26-23-54/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:32+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-26-23-54</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Vendredi 26 Juin 2015 23:54:44
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
your words can turn bad luck into happiness! You are like these fairies in the fairy tales. Yes, you are really good, good as a person, and good to me. I want to be like you :-) And I will be good to you forever.
</p>


<p>
It is really important to have people who help us. I also met several people who were good and very helpful. For instance, in Analysis I, one of the first courses I took, my tutor helped me a lot. I could ask him many questions, not only about the course, but also about which courses to take in the following years, which mathematical areas are interesting and so on. We kept in touch throughout the years. Later on, we ended up doing our PhDs with the same supervisor. So we met and discussed our progress on our theses. And at some point, we even shared an office. Now, he is still in academics, but he shifted his focus to numerics. Every time I meet him, it is always a pleasure to talk to him. And like you, I feel very thankful. Also, I think as we grow older and get more senior, it is our turn to help beginners. So once this older student of Q finishes his PhD, will you then be the most senior student of Q? Concerning your idea, I think a present is a very nice gesture, and Q's student will certainly be delighted. Do you know what his plans are after his PhD?
</p>


<p>
Four girls? Really? That's tough. I wonder how the one guy survives :-D No, seriously, you have a much stronger mind than me. I had to share my office with one person during my PhD, and no matter whether girl or boy, I always felt that I could not concentrate that well. So in the end, I mostly worked at home. My colleagues would then joke that they never see me working :-) And it's quite funny, I got so used to the working environment at home, my desk, my bookshelf, my chair, ..., that for some time, I thought that I would never be able to work somewhere else. Now, having moved around several times, I am much more relaxed. It is possible to get used to different settings. But then, as I write this, I have to laugh, because when I started in London, I asked a moving company to bring my desk, my bookshelf and my chair from Germany :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-25 23:51]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-25-23-51/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:31+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-25-23-51</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Thursday, June 25, 2015 11:51 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
You have offered me so many happiness and energy! If these are also the things I could give you, I would more than happy to do so, and I will do it forever :-)
</p>


<p>
Yes, we can really learn a lot of from our failure. The mistake I made few days ago really gave me a deeper vision of the problem, and let me know which direction I could choose and which could not. So tomorrow, I tried another method and it seems that it works this time, or at least till now, like you said, I should check it more times in case I make a mistake again :-) Q will come back to B next week for the defense of a student of him who is two years older than me, he really helped me a lot this year past, since this is my first year in Ph.D, in the beginning, I had trouble in mathematics and he is always willing to help by discussing the problems with me and I gained a lot. So I'm wondering to express my thanks to him, maybe I will give him a bouquet with a card of thanks :-)
</p>


<p>
You make your explanation very clear this time :-) I understand it now. Speaking of working with noise, I am quite good at it now :-) I have told you that there are five students in our office, and we have four girls! But other offices for Ph.D students almost have no girls. And there are two in our office can really talk :-D Sometimes for several hours! I'm saying this doesn't means I don't like them, in the contrary, they are very nice. It's just, you know, girls always talk a lot when they are together, sometimes even include me, but, only "sometimes" :-) Now, with a year of training, I think I can absorb to my work in any situations :-D
</p>


<p>
You had bad luck this Monday, this is the thing we can not avoid, it is out of our control. But the things we could control is our attitude to face it, look at you, you have found the amazing views others may not see :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-25 00:18]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-25-00-18/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:30+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-25-00-18</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Thu, 25 Jun 2015 00:18:04 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
in our hearts and in our thoughts, we will always be together, forever. And compared to infinity, two months does not feel that long... But you are right, having things to do helps a lot. For me, last week passed away quickly, because I had a conference. And I'm sure that once you are in China, time will pass faster for you. Thinking about it, I find myself in a paradoxical situation. On the one hand, when I think about you, I just feel a strong desire to meet you again, and time does not pass at all. On the other hand, the thought of you gives me motivation and energy to work really, really hard, and when I am completely absorbed in my work, then time does pass faster. So, in total, does time pass more quickly or more slowly?
</p>


<p>
Oh yes, that experience you are describing is an absolute classic, I think that every mathematician goes through these situations many many times. I remember once when I was doing my PhD, I thought I had a brilliant idea, which would solve a main problem of my thesis. So I made an appointment with my advisor the next morning. But later in the evening, when I thought about it again, my argument fell apart. So the meeting the next day was very embarrassing. Fortunately, my advisor was sympathetic and not angry with me :-) Some time after that, I did manage to solve the problem. And you can imagine that I checked everything many many times :-D Although these failures seem to lead nowhere, I think that they are actually quite important. We can learn a lot and gain some insights, in particular if we understand what exactly went wrong, and why.
</p>


<p>
I came back yesterday night. It was a short conference, and for me, it was even shorter than expected: My plan was to take a flight to Aberdeen arriving around lunchtime. However, at the airport they told me that my flight was canceled. There was even no explanation why. So they put me in a flight to Edinburgh, and I had to go by train to Aberdeen, which took another three hours or so. In the end, I arrived around dinnertime. Fortunately, my talk was the next morning. At first, I was really annoyed. But at some point, I told myself that there is nothing I could do, so I just relaxed and took it easy. And actually, the train ride from Edinburgh to Aberdeen is very nice, most of it is along the coast, with a view of the sea. So at least not everything was bad.
</p>


<p>
Oh, you're right, I didn't explain the moving activity well :-) Let me try again: Currently, our offices are on one side of the building which faces the place where the new building will be built. While they are constructing the new building, they also have to work on that part of the old building, maybe to connect the two. Besides, since our old offices are close to the construction site, it would be very noisy. That is why we have to move to another part of the old maths building. Once the new building is finished, we move there, and they work on the remaining part of the old maths building. So when you visit me, the maths department will be a complete mess. But I suppose we are not going to spend that much time in my office anyway ;-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-23 19:27]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-23-19-27/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:29+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-23-19-27</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, June 23, 2015 7:27 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I can totally understand your excitement, because I feel exactly the same as you :-) But from now, it seems that two months is really a longtime, maybe it's better to keep myself busy so that the time will pass faster (at least I hope so). Yes, "forever" is a beautiful word for me, it is a word with strong emotion and I also find a similar word in mathematics, which is the symbol of "infinity" :-) I like this symbol very much, and some times ago, I found out that a girl in our office has the tattoo of this symbol, I got excited and told her I also like it.
</p>


<p>
Yesterday afternoon I thought I might have solved the problem of the main theorem I'm working on, I got so happy, but I checked it last night, it turned out I had made a huge mistake, so now, I have to start all over again :-) Will you do back tonight? And how is it?
</p>


<p>
I'm sorry, but I didn't get it, why you need to move out when another building is started to be built :-) A maths building with a roofgarden? That must be wonderful. And I don't know that Black Forest cake is that sweet, maybe just because the cake I tasted is not authentic enough :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-21 14:57]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-21-14-57/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:28+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-21-14-57</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Dimanche 21 Juin 2015 14:57:10
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: bon anniversaire
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
this is wonderful news indeed! When I read that you got your visa, I could feel my heart beating faster than usual, so big is my excitement! I'm relieved that everything worked out. Well done :-) A look at the calendar tells me that there two months left now. So time does pass, slowly, but steadily. And then, we'll meet again! I feel such a desire to see you, it is hard to describe in words, the feeling is so strong...
</p>


<p>
I recently came across a song by The Beach Boys called "Forever", and I immediately liked it. Maybe it's mainly because of the lyrics, they start like this "If every word I said Could make you laugh I'd talk forever I ask the sky just what we had It shone forever If the song I sing to you Could fill your heart with joy I'd sing forever ..."
</p>


<p>
My first time in O was in 2009, so seven years ago. There were two years with two meetings. Some time ago, a colleague celebrated his first birthday in O, he has spent more than 52 weeks there! Yes, Black Forest cake is famous for that region, and it's very popular. I also like it, but it's very sweet, maybe a bit too much if I'm honest :-)
</p>


<p>
Next month, they start to build our new maths building. It will be next to the old one. Once the new building is finished, they will renovate the old one. So next week, we have to move. The whole construction is supposed to take two years, but people already gossip that it will take much longer. Hopefully, it won't be too noisy. It will definitely bring some inconveniences, for instance, I will have to temporarily share an office with a colleague. But the new building is supposed to be very nice, it will even have a roofgarden :-)
</p>


<p>
Yes, it is better to teach less so that you can concentrate on the quality of your teaching. I think it will be a very interesting and helpful experience. As always, every challenge helps you to develop and improve. And I'm sure that you will try your best :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
