<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Epitaph for One Love]]></title>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-10-01T22:12:09+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Shy]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-21 12:16]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-21-12-16/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:57+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-21-12-16</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Thursday, May 21, 2015 12:16 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
In fact, your passion for mathematics also gives me energy for what I am doing now, and I feel lucky that I could work with things I'm really interested in.
</p>


<p>
Your description about the day in Oxford also makes me enchanted, and anyway, I really want to go there by myself. :-) Yes, you are right, I am a fan of Harry Potter since I was a child, for me, the magic world in it is one of the most important memories of my childhood. So your Oxford trip makes me feel excited like a child! I'm thinking about maybe I could go to London in the late August, and then visit a friend in Reading, but I should ask the visa issues first.
</p>


<p>
"These people were great artists because they had tragic lives, or they had tragic lives because they were great artists", you have said exactly the words that I want to say. And that's the reason why I like these people so much, I am so happy that you feel the same! There was a romance between 徐志摩 and 林徽因, A Snowflake's Happiness is one his poems, written to LIN, have you read?
</p>


<p>
You mean Le Papillon? The story of a smart little girl and an old man? yes, I love it, quite warm and funny :-D By the way, "the children version" of Dead Poets Society we have talked about, its name is Les Choristes.
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-20 00:17]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-20-00-17/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:56+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-20-00-17</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mercredi 20 Mai 2015 00:17:43
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
it makes me feel warm and happy that you share my passion for mathematics. Thank you! :-)
</p>


<p>
I just came back from Oxford. Since it was my first time in Oxford, I took a bit of time before my seminar talk to walk around. Among other things, I was at the Christ Church, where they shot scenes for Harry Potter. Unfortunately, the dining hall was closed for visitors. Then I met with my host and gave a seminar talk. Afterwards, we had dinner in St John's College. That was like in the movies, or like turning back time. The ceilings were high, on the walls were paintings of important members of the college, people were wearing gowns, and there were prayers in Latin. I still feel enchanted ... By the way, do you like Harry Potter a lot? I saw that your skype username has h in it ...
</p>


<p>
I have the same feeling as you about artists like 萧红 or 林徽因. Not only were their lives short, but - at least from what I read - full of strong emotions, and tragic love. Even more extreme is 顾城. When I first read his story and how it ended, I was very emotional and felt extremely sad. I wonder whether these people were great artists because they had tragic lives, or they had tragic lives because they were great artists. Talking about 林徽因, I found out that she was close to 徐志摩. I have recently read a few poems he wrote, some of them are very beautiful, I like them a lot.
</p>


<p>
Actually, I haven't watched A Beautiful Mind yet. But since you like it so much, I will watch it; it's on top of my To-do list. I'm sure that you know more movies than me, which is good, because then I can ask you for recommendations :-D The other day, I also had a movie in mind which you probably like, its name is Papillon. Do you know it?
</p>


<p>
Yes, I'm going to the Symposium, which is for five days in the first half of August. The rest of August I will be in London.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-18 17:23]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-18-17-23/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:55+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-18-17-23</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Monday, May 18, 2015 5:23 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Your desprition of mathematics is just as wonderful as it should be! You could really appreciate the beauty of mathematics. And, you have choosed really great movies! In fact,I have heard something about the movie Imitation game from one of my friends the other day, and I thought you might like it because you told me that you are interested in number theory. What a coincidence, you tell me today that you have already watched and like it! Speak of the movie about mathematicians, I think The beautiful mind is also great, of course you have watched it cause it is classical.
</p>


<p>
Yes, when reading about the life of 萧红, it aways makes me feel a kind of regretful, she has the talent in literature, however she lived in a wrong time. And I have the same feeling about 林徽因 whom we have already talked about. Why does beautiful life awalys so short! As for the work of 萧红, I haven't read one before, but 呼兰河传 is one of her most famous novels I think, maybe you could have a try.
</p>


<p>
I wasn't lucky as you were during the long flight last week, the little tele in my seat was broken, it doesn't work at all... :-)
</p>


<p>
I haven't decided yet where to go after the conference in Copenhagen. Do you have a symposium in Norway in August? Will you go back to London after that or you have other plans?
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-18 10:47]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-18-10-47/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:54+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-18-10-47</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Lundi 18 Mai 2015 10:47:32
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, exactly as you wrote, I arrived safely in London last night. Usually, I really hate long flights, but I was lucky this time with the movie selection. I watched The Imitation Game about Alan Turing, The Theory of Everything about Stephen Hawkings and 黄金时代 about 萧红. All these characters made an impression on me, especially their creativity. Mathematics is actually a very creative subject. I think about it as colours of the rainbow: The two extremes are red and violet, but somehow they belong together. Mathematics is also positioned at two extreme points, it is the most logical of all sciences, but also as creative as an art. And these two aspects belong together, one cannot be without the other. Unfortunately, this is sometimes difficult to explain to non-mathematicians. Coming back to 萧红, she must have been a very interesting character, who had a (short) life full of ups and downs. I think I'd like to read something she wrote. Do you know some of her work?
</p>


<p>
In the UK, every PhD student has to be examined every year. This is to give them feedback on their progress. So I'm going to examine someone else's student today.
</p>


<p>
Is there a particular place you would like to go for vacation this summer?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes, and a nice week for you as well,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-17 15:44]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-17-15-44/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:53+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-17-15-44</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Sunday, May 17, 2015 3:44 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I suppose that you will arrive London tonight, hope everything will be fine. Yes, that is exactly the conference I'm talking about, I have already signed up, since it will begin on 16th August, I have to return France as soon as the seminar in Wuhan ends. So no time for a vacation in Wuhan, but, as you have said, it's worth it. And I'm thinking about maybe I could have a vacation somewhere after that.
</p>


<p>
It seems that you enjoy your stay in Shanghai, although I can't stand the skyscraper, but I really like the bike tour! However, It's a kind of hard to enjoy due to the crowdedness and traffic in the big city of China :-)
</p>


<p>
You have mentioned you are going to examine a PHD student, are you going to have a student or something? And I wish you could spend your next week smoothly.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-16 14:50]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-16-14-50/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:52+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-16-14-50</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Sat, 16 May 2015 14:50:27 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I'm delighted to hear that you arrived safely. Enjoy the fresh air, the empty (or almost empty) streets and the quietness. And yes, Copenhagen is a great place, in particular for operator algebras. I know quite a few people there. Are you talking about this conference "Young Mathematicians in C*-Algebras"? That would be great. Haagerup is famous, and the other speaker, Stuart White, is also very good and gives very nice talks. So, yes, you should go.
</p>


<p>
Today is my last night in Shanghai. I really enjoyed my stay here. Apart from mathematics, we also went to Shanghai and had a look around. We went up on this skyscraper which used to be the tallest. It is about 470 meters high, and we were on the top floor. Do you feel shaky reading these lines? I was OK up there, but I was also quite happy when we were down on the ground again. They have now built a taller building, more than 600 meters high, next to it. It is a crazy way to spend money... We also had a bike tour in Shanghai. I'm quite proud that I survived ;-)
</p>


<p>
All in all, I really enjoyed my visit to China. I got lots of inspiration, and will return to London with many many precious memories. This should give me enough energy to carry me through sleepness nights answering students' emails...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-15 16:58]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-15-16-58/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:51+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-15-16-58</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Friday, May 15, 2015 4:58 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I arrived B yesterday, everything goes fine. And I'am happy that I can breath the fresh air again! Today one of my colleague told me there is a Mini-course in Copenhagen during the summer vacation, one of the major speaker is Haagerup, I think it's interesting, maybe I will try to sign up.
</p>


<p>
Have you finished your trip in Shanghai? But it seems that you have to throw yourself into the really busy week as soon as you go back to London. 100 email each day?! That makes me hard to imagine how can you respond all of them :-) Anyway, wish you a good luck.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-14 01:34]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-14-01-34/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:50+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-14-01-34</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Jeudi 14 Mai 2015 01:34:00
<br>
Objet: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I'm glad that your father is well. Your parents must be very proud of you; they are fortunate to have such a daughter like you :-)
</p>


<p>
You are a detailed observer. Yes, I wake up early, but I also go to bed early, so that's OK. My talk yesterday was good. It was similar to the one I gave in Wuhan, so preparation was easy.
</p>


<p>
When I get back to London, my first week will be very busy: On Monday, I have to examine a PhD student, on Tuesday, I'm giving a seminar talk in Oxford, and the exam for my own lectures takes place on Friday. Last year, shortly before the exam, my students sent me 100 emails each day with questions about the exam. And directly after the exam, I spent several days doing nothing else but sleeping, drinking, eating and marking exams. I fear that this year, I have to get prepared for a similar battle. Once that is done, I can enjoy life again ...
</p>


<p>
Good luck with the paper!
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-13 19:41]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-13-19-41/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:49+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-13-19-41</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Wednesday, May 13, 2015 1:41 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I notice that you get up quite early, I hope you have got over the jet-lag :-). I'm glad to hear that the interesting talk tomorow gave you some inspiration, and how was your talk today morning?
</p>


<p>
Thank you for your concern, my father has finished the small operation today, the result turns out to be quite succesful, so I think I can leave at ease tomorrow.
</p>


<p>
Hopefully, some improvements could be made with the paper I'm working on in the next two mouths in B :-) After that, I hope I could arrange myself a trip, maybe I would have a chance to meet you... Well, a lot plans, I expect that they all could be realised!
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-13 06:06]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-13-06-06/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:48+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-13-06-06</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mercredi 13 Mai 2015 06:06:26
<br>
Objet: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
a new sister! Wow! Awesome! This trip to China is exceeding all my expectations. Honestly, before I left London, I was very uncertain what to expect, especially from my visit to Wuhan. I would never have imagined that I would come back to London having found a new sister. What a wonderful world.
</p>


<p>
As we discussed, life is full of coincidences and wonders. Actually, I originally wanted to visit Wuhan in the week after Shanghai, and we would have missed each other. Also, there were problems with my visa. So it was by chance that things worked out. Thinking about it, I feel amazed how little control we have over the things that happen in our lives. At the same time, this makes me realize that we should really make use of the few chances we get.
</p>


<p>
Thanks for adding me in Skype. I accepted, so we can skype whenever you feel like it. Just let me know.
</p>


<p>
I'm having a good time in Shanghai. Yesterday there was a very interesting talk, and I hope that I can use some of the material for my own research. Today it's my turn to give a talk.
</p>


<p>
I hope that you are having a few nice days back at home with your parents. Didn't you say that your father had to do some sort of operation? I hope that everything went well and that he is doing fine. If I'm not mistaken, you are going back to France tomorrow. Of course, I wish you a safe trip, or: "Gute Reise" :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-11 22:54]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-22-54/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:47+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-22-54</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Monday, May 11, 2015 4:54 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I am really excited to have a new brother! Yes, you are really good, don't be modest, that's the reality :-). I have the same feeling as you do, maybe we have many things in common. Speak of last week, I should thank Q for giving me the chance to know you and talk to you, I really cherish it, there isn't any inconvenience at all. So you are welcome anytime, I mean it. Maybe I can find a chance to go to London, I am expecting it.
</p>


<p>
Yes, S also does maths, he took M2 in Paris last year, but he changed his direction to f this year and went to B. In fact, I feel that you have much in common :-)
</p>


<p>
By the way, I have sent you a request for adding in Skype, hope you have well recieved it.
</p>


<p>
Bonne nuit,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-11 22:04]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-22-04/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:46+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-22-04</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Lundi 11 Mai 2015 22:04:43
<br>
Objet: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
you are really nice. If you keep making me compliments like that, one day I will lose my sense of reality ;-) More seriously, I think one of the best things about being a mathematician is that you can travel around and meet interesting people. And I think that people are the biggest source of inspiration. But then, it is not easy to find others with similar ideas and points of view. With you, I had that feeling of being close, almost like brother and sister. Actually, what a wonderful thought: To have you as my second sister! I hope you do not mind that I think about you that way...
</p>


<p>
My skype username is t_x. But I am offline almost all the time, so you would have to let me know in advance if you would like to talk.
</p>


<p>
S? Hmmm, that is indeed funny, what a coincidence :-) Is he also doing maths? I am sure that I will like him. First, I thought that it would be great to visit you guys in B. But then thinking about it again, I realized that I would cause inconveniences; and I have already caused so many inconveniences for you last week in Wuhan that it will be difficult to pay back. Maybe it would really be better if you and S could visit me in London, so that I can be the host...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-11 13:08]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-13-08/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:45+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-13-08</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Monday, May 11, 2015 7:08 AM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
How generous you are! I feel really happy that I can make a friend like you and I enjoy writting to you. In fact, I have been using skype for few years, you can tell me your username that I can add you.
</p>


<p>
It will be nice if it is possible for you to pay a visit to B, it is a small but beautiful city, I can also introduce my boyfriend to you there, his name is S (has the same pronunciation as your name in Germany :-) ), I think you will also like him.
</p>


<p>
I agree with your opinion on the internet, it makes our lives more convenient, but in the meantime, it also makes us less willing to think. In the past, we communicated by letter in which we put a lot of thought, so is the email today. However, if we communicate in other ways, like "Wechat", it is less thoughtful.
</p>


<p>
Well, hope you have a good trip in Shanghai :-D.
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-11 07:34]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-07-34/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:44+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-11-07-34</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Lundi 11 Mai 2015 07:34:20
<br>
Objet: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
thank you so much for your email, it has put a big smile on my face and made me really happy :-D
</p>


<p>
London, Wuhan; B would be another option. In a month, I will go to a conference in O. This is in the Black Forest, near F. And I think that it is not too far from B. Moreover, I have a colleague in Orléans whom I am planning to visit at some point this year. So there are opportunities...
</p>


<p>
In the meantime, 21st century provides solutions if we want to talk although we are far away. I am thinking of Skype, or its Chinese analogue for online phone calls (I know it exists, but have forgotten the name). If you like the idea and want to give it a try, just let me know.
</p>


<p>
By the way, talking about 21st century, I was very much relieved that the internet connection here in my hotel in Shanghai is much faster than the one I had before. This makes me feel like coming back to 2015. At the same time, it is frightening to see how much we depend on the internet nowadays.
</p>


<p>
Have a nice week,
<br>
and best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-10 20:41]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-10-20-41/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:43+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-10-20-41</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Sunday, May 10, 2015 2:41 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Well, I'm glad to hear that everything goes fine:-D. I also really enjoy the time with you and I am happy you feel the same. I am sure we will find another chance to meet each other, maybe in London, maybe in Wuhan. Keep in touch~
</p>


<p>
Viele Grüße,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-10 18:21]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-10-18-21/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:42+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-10-18-21</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Dimanche 10 Mai 2015 18:21:11
<br>
Objet: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I just arrived safely in Shanghai. Everything went fine.
</p>


<p>
Let me thank you heartily for all your help in Wuhan. It has been a wonderful visit, but I especially enjoyed meeting you and talking to you. Hopefully, we will meet again soon. As I said, I would be more than happy to arrange a visit for you in London if you find the time. Let us keep in touch.
</p>


<p>
Merci beaucoup!
<br>
Amitiés,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
