<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Epitaph for One Love]]></title>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-10-02T11:40:59+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Shy]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-09 10:56]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-09-10-56/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:17+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-09-10-56</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, June 9, 2015 10:56 AM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I also heard the news after I told you this movie, I feel sorry for it, especially after seeing what he has suffered from his mental illness and how they faced it together...
</p>


<p>
Although I'm a little afraid of the sadness that may come after watch "Amour", I sure I will do it someday, since I don't see sad as an emotion we should avoid. I still remember that in my high school, I watched a movie which has a very tragic ending, I was depressed for several days, everything seemed hopeless to me , even my friend found out there was something wrong with me, and asked me what happened :-) Now, I have to laugh when recalling this. Yes, now, I still get heartbreaking for the books I read, the movies I watched, however, I won't feel hopeless anymore, contrarily, I see it as a way to make us cherish what we have. Speaking of high school, I really don't like most of part of it. Yes, sometimes we got good moments, but most of time it seemed like everything we did is just for passing the university entrance exam (高考), and it is a exam really boring :-( We repeat the same thing everything, which now I feel like wasting of time and life. Ok, I shouldn't be so negative, like what I've just said, I really cherish the life I have now, doing the things I like :-)
</p>


<p>
Yesterday, I received the email, they told me I will teach "Analysis" next semester, it contains both lecture and seminar, so there are much to prepare I suppose. Ok, now I will say, See you tomorrow :-D
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-07 21:09]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-07-21-09/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:16+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-07-21-09</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Dimanche 7 Juin 2015 21:09:15
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
thank you for your encouraging words about teaching, that's very kind of you :-)
</p>


<p>
You don't have to watch "Amour" if you don't want to, I can perfectly understand your feelings. In my case, I watched the movie by chance, I haven't read about it before, so there was no courage involved, only naivety :-D About heartbreaking stories, do you know the Japanese writer Banana Yoshimoto? (Banana is not her real name.) I read Kitchen and Moonlight Shadow by her. These are really moving and heartbreaking. The first story still gave me the feeling of some hope, while the second one just made me sad...
</p>


<p>
Coming back to movies, I watched "A Beautiful Mind" yesterday. What can I say? I knew a bit about Nash's mathematical achievements, but I didn't know about his mental illness. I'm impressed that in spite of his sufferings, he became such a great mathematician! Or maybe the illness and his ingenuity were connected, maybe it was his illness which allowed him to do things normal people would never be able to do. Anyway, it seems like a very high price to pay. Nash must have been a special character, in positive and negative ways. I learned that he and his wife died in a car accident this month, coming home from Norway where he received the Abel Prize. Tragic, isn't it?
</p>


<p>
Yes, that's great, you can call me via Skype on Wednesday, at 20:00 local time in France (which is 19:00 London time). It's a good time for me. So I'll just wait for you, and make sure that I'm online and logged into Skype.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-06 18:19]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-06-18-19/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:15+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-06-18-19</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Saturday, June 6, 2015 6:19 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Thank you for your stories, the negative one and the positive one. Reading about that you just seat there and got trembling after your first lecture, it makes me laugh, since it reminds me of my same experience last year when I did my oral defense for master thesis :-) I'm sure you learned a lot from last year, asking questions is a good way to keep attention up, that's the way I expected my teacher to do when I was undergraduate. And the beauty, the importance of the proofs, that requires more understanding or admiring of what you teach, not everyone can do that, so I guess that's reason you get the positive feedback this year :-) Ah, you have got a student? I must say congratulations to you! Perhaps you can tell more about it when I call you? I'm wondering maybe I will call you in skype Wednesday night to say Gute Reise to you:-), around eight clock( in France), is that Ok for you?
</p>


<p>
In fact, I knew "Amour" because I saw a short review of someone, it writes also the main two parts in the film, the love and the pain. When facing the subject like illness and age, I always feel fragile, so I'm not sure I won't be overwhelmed by the heartbreaking seeing this film, that's the reason why I haven't watched it yet. It really needs courage :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-06 00:28]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-06-00-28/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:14+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-06-00-28</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Sat, 06 Jun 2015 00:28:02 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, absolutely, feedback is very important. If it's positive, then that's nice, but if it's negative (and honest), then we can actually learn even more. For instance, last year, my teaching was not so good. It was my first time teaching in the UK, and I was not familiar with the material of the module. So I focused on giving good lectures, explaining all the proofs in detail. For those students who paid attention, it was fine, but quite a few got bored and even started to get noisy; also, students were afraid of the proofs, especially in the exam. This year, I changed things a bit. Not the material of the module, and I also did all the proofs, but I would ask questions during my lectures to keep the attention up, and I would summarize the ideas of very long proofs. I even spent half an hour to discuss the importance, and also the beauty, of proofs. These little changes made quite a difference. I think that teaching or giving talks is a matter of practice and experience. I remember quite well the first talk I gave in our research seminar. I did a lot of preparations, and was quite nervous. And after the talk, I sat for hours in my room, my hands still trembling from the agitation :-) Thinking back, I have to laugh about myself, because in the meantime, I gave lots of talks, and feel more confident about it. So the first time may not be easy, but once you started to teach, I am sure you will get more and more confident.
</p>


<p>
Yes, I remember the scene. And I had to smile that you went to the restaurant and watched the sea. I don't think it's stupid, because that's exactly the sort of thing I can imagine myself doing :-) The only problem is that New Zealand is quite far away :-D And yes, I like "Amour". It's touching in both ways, in a nice way when you see the couple's love, but also in a heartbreaking way when you see their pain... Yes, yes, I won't say more, since you want to watch the movie :-)
</p>


<p>
If you were my PhD student, then I would be facing the following problem: On the one hand, I would want the best for you, which means that I would have to be very strict and demanding, but on the other hand, I would be afraid of making you unhappy, or that you would be angry with me. So in the end, I probably wouldn't know what to do at all ;-) More seriously, I still have to learn at lot when it comes to supervising PhD students. Actually, I just got a new student this week; we had our first meeting three days ago.
</p>


<p>
By the way, I'm going to Germany next Thursday, to visit family and for a conference. Would you like to skype before I go? I'd be available anytime you like, just let me know.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-04 21:06]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-04-21-06/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:13+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-04-21-06</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Thursday, June 4, 2015 9:06 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
It's funny, but truly sometimes if we get some feedback from others, it really encourges us, although we don't do it for rewards at the first time. And I think maybe the happiness as a teacher is to know that you really help them to do well, I'm happy to read that your students like you, perhaps it's because you do have made wonderful lectures :-) If I were few years younger, maybe I would choose you as my Ph.D. superviser :-D Hmm... Q won't be happy to hear this, haha. More seriously, I'm still not sure if I can get the chance to teach next semester, but if I get, there is still much to prepare during this summer I suppose, since I've never tried before.
</p>


<p>
"The Intouchables", in fact, I like this movie very much, but I didn't notice its music, I should have paid more attention, since now, I find them quite good. Two people who have totally different backgrounds , but they are a really perfect couple, maybe just because they both know how to respect the others. Do you remember in the end of film, the scene when the man finally meets his penfriend in a restaurant and the scenery seen from their table? The beach and the wave... They are quite impressive for me, then I found out that it is shot at the coast of Cabourg. So last year, I went to that place, found the restaurant in the movie and watched the sea from the same angle :-)It sounds a little stupide, but anyway, it's quite wonderful! Perhaps, one day, you can also experience the scenery in Lord of ring in New Zealand :-)
</p>


<p>
I heard about "Amour" before, but I haven't seen yet, since you like, I will see it.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-03 22:34]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-03-22-34/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:12+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-03-22-34</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Mercredi 3 Juin 2015 22:34:07
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
awesome, that's great news! Thanks for letting me know about your bookings, and I wish you good luck in Paris, let's hope that everything will be fine. If you need to take a local train, to Reading or somewhere else, we can always buy tickets during your visit, that's easy. And yes, I also want to see you again, I want it sooo much :-) Is it really only a month since we've met in Wuhan? I really have to force myself not to think about you all the time, because that only makes the waiting time pass even more slowly :-(
</p>


<p>
I just finished checking today. Not only do we have to mark our own exams, but we also have to check the ones of our colleagues. That just means going through the scripts and making sure that the points add up correctly, and that the examiner has not overlooked something. When I said that marking is terrible, then checking is even worse. It's so boring and monotonous, you just have to turn pages and add up numbers, like a calculator. But it has to be done. Anyway, it's over now. Maybe I shouldn't be so negative, since teaching my module this year was actually quite nice. My students were pretty good, at least that was my impression. And it's very rewarding to see students do well! There was one student who shook my hand and told me that it was an honour to be taught be me, he did that twice, and every time we meet he always greets me with a big smile and waves :-D And yesterday, a group of students came to my office to thank me for the teaching :-) So, yes, if you could do a bit of teaching, I think that would be a good experience.
</p>


<p>
Just as you say, Sissel's voice is like an angel. Very beautiful. Enya's voice also is like that. I first heard Enya in "Lord of the Rings". These are epic movies. Particularly impressive is the scenery, they filmed in New Zealand. I've never been there, but that's definitely a place I'd like to go. New Zealand and Australia must simply be beautiful. Ludovico Enaudi's music appears in the movie "The Intouchables", that's a French movie about a person in a wheelchair and a guy who takes care of him. It's quite moving to see how they help each other. Talking about French movies, I recently saw "Amour", also a very touching movie about a couple who loves each other until a very old age. Do you know it?
</p>


<p>
Wonderful, that rainbow was a very nice welcoming present for you in B! And now I also have a beautiful picture in my mind, the rainbow with its bright colours, the fresh air after the rain, the rays of sunshine breaking through the clouds, ..., and you, admiring the beauty of the rainbow, trying to touch it...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-02 23:28]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-02-23-28/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:11+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-02-23-28</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, June 2, 2015 11:28 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
I'm happy that I'm quite efficient tonight, I have accomplished the applying procedures on the internet and booked all the tickets I need for application. Concerning the ticket to Reading, because after I told my friend that I get a chance to meet her, she prefers maybe go somewhere else near London with me instead of Reading, and she still haven't made her mind yet. My appointment in Paris will be at next Friday, hope everything will be fine. If nothing goes wrong, I will arrive London st-Pancras at 15h30 23th August. Writing about this makes me excited again, I can't wait to see you again:-)
</p>


<p>
Yes, Sissel's voice is just like angel. Where does "should it matter" from? Humm, it's a good question...You don't know since I have made a mistake! :-):-), ok, the thing should be when I watched Titanic, the fascinating vocal during the movie made me obsessed, I looked it up, it's devoted by Sissel, so then I get many other her pieces, "should it matter" is one of my favorites. You say that you listened Ludovico Einaudi and Enya in the movies at the first time, in which one? Moreover, I'm very happy to know that you use the Canon to wake you up every day, because it is a music we both like, and that's indeed a wonderful start of a day.
</p>


<p>
Speaking of the rainbow after the rain, I still remember the experience when I saw a rainbow the first time after I arrived B. That may be the most wonderful rainbow I have ever seen, it had exactly seven colors, every one of them is so bright, and it seemed so closed, and I felt that I can even touch it by my hand! I have been to the sea for a few times, but I never got to the chance to see a sunset or sunrise. Now I have got a beautiful image in my mind, siting near the plage, waiting for sun to get it's head out, quietly...
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-06-01 20:38]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-01-20-38/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:10+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-06-01-20-38</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Lundi 1 Juin 2015 20:38:08
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I really had to smile when I read your description how you discover music, because that's exactly the way I usually do it as well! And thinking about it, the first time I listened to Ludovico Einaudi and Enya was actually in movies. Yes, Pachelbel's "Canon in D Major" is beautiful, I use it as an alarm sound to wake me up in the morning - it's a nice way to start the day. And thanks for "Should it matter" (from Sissel, I suppose), the singer's voice is so beautiful, I had to listen to the song again, and again, and again... Forgive my ignorance, but from which movie is "Should it matter"?
</p>


<p>
What you describe as your dream, the waves, the wind, the stars, or also a beautiful moon, a colourful rainbow after the rain, all these are wonderful. And the great thing is: These little wonders are there, for us to admire, we just have to open our eyes and see with our hearts... I'm really happy - as you say - to have found a companion in you who can also appreciate these beauties. Well, let's hope that our dreams may come true :-)
</p>


<p>
Have you watched a sunrise, or sunset, at the sea? I did that when I was in the US. While I was there for my research visit, I had a bit of time left to do a tour through the country, and I was lucky enough to see a sunrise in Miami and a sunset in San Francisco, very beautiful.
</p>


<p>
Your travel plan sounds perfect. I definitely look forward to meeting you again :-) Please let me know once you have news concerning your visa, or once you have booked your tickets. By the way, since the train from London to Reading is a local one, it's maybe the easiest if I book that for you. If you want, I can do that once you've booked the big trip from France to the UK.
</p>


<p>
Remember when you taught me this character, 犇? You'll definitely make a very good Chinese teacher. And thinking about how you said to me before on my last evening in Wuhan, I'm convinced that you'll also be a very good German student. So, all I hope is that I can be equally good ;-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-31 16:31]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-31-16-31/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:09+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-31-16-31</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Sunday, May 31, 2015 4:23 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Although I haven't decided the all the details of my trip, since the train information of September is still unavailable, but most likely, I will take the train at 10:00 from Besancon, then the Eurostar to London in 23th August, and go to Reading in the morning of 31th :-)
</p>


<p>
My way to choose music is quite "random" actually, sometimes I just run across a piece of music, if I enjoy it very much, maybe I will fall in love with it after that :-) I like Pachelbel's "Canon in D Major", most of the pieces in Tschaikovski's "The seasons", and also Schumann's "Traeumerei"! And I also get a lot good musics from the movies, for example, "Moon river", "Give me some sunshine", "Should it matter", and almost all the musics in Miyazaki's movies composed by Joe Hisaishi... I notice that Yiruma also wrote some pieces to movies, "Kiss the rain" is beautiful.
</p>


<p>
You are so lucky to have this unforgettable experience in such a wonderful place! And your description makes me enchanted, again! For me, maybe it existed only in my dream, the bird song, the wash of the waves, even the sound of trees swept by the wind, the sky with countless stars... And I really hope that one day my dreams could come true :-) Maybe in Corsica!
</p>


<p>
If you could teach me German, I will be more than happy. So I guess I will try my best to be a good student :-) And, if you need any help in Chinese or French, I'm always glad to do all the things I can.
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-30 01:06]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-30-01-06/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:08+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-30-01-06</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Sat, 30 May 2015 01:06:56 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, a visa for visit is fine. Concerning your travel dates, you can arrive at any date you like, I'm flexible. I guess you will want to go back to B after Copenhagen, so maybe you can come to London on 22 or 23 August. Just choose a date which is convenient for you, so that you don't have to rush. And for the departure date, I don't need to go back to Germany early, it would be enough if I take a flight on 31 August, in the afternoon or in the evening. If you visit your friend in Reading afterwards, you'll probably go by train. Then you could for instance take a train in the morning on 31 August, so that I can bring you to the station. This way we'll have at least a week.
</p>


<p>
Yes, I like music, classical music, but really all sort of music. And I'm not an expert, I just enjoy it. If you want some concrete pieces, I for instance like Schumann's "Traeumerei", Debussy's "Claire de lune", Dvorak's "New World Symphony" or Dvorak's String quartet called "American". The composer I told you about is Haydn, he wrote many piano sonatas, most of which I like as well. But I also like popular music, for instance Yiruma or Ludovico Einaudi, and also Enya. What pieces of music do you like?
</p>


<p>
Talking about music brings back some of my best childhood memories: I was a member of a scout club, and there were camps during the holidays. Usually we went hiking, and at night, we would sit around a bonfire, someone played the guitar and we would sing songs. It was wonderful. I still remember one trip to Corsica (La Corse), where we went hiking. One night, we went to the beach, just lied there next to the sea, the sky was clear, and we watched the stars. I've never seen so many stars, and they were so bright and seemed so close. It was incredibly beautiful. At that moment, I realized how small we are... I've always wanted to go back there again. Maybe we can go there together? Wouldn't that be wonderful, lying on the beach, listening to the waves and watching the stars together. Oh, it's a dream... But it's a very nice one...
</p>


<p>
People say that German is a difficult language, but I'm sure not for you, since you seem to be talented; I'm still impressed that your French is already very advanced, much better than mine :-) Here is the deal: I'll teach you German, and you help me improve my Chinese and my French. How is that?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-29 15:01]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-29-15-01/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:07+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-29-15-01</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Friday, May 29, 2015 3:01 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Les Choristes is a movie I have watched for several times, and every time I will be moved by the way how the teacher inspires those so-called "problem sutudents" and also by their clear and pure voice. Do you like the music in the movie? In fact, the children in this movie, they are real singers from a chorus called Les Petits chanteurs de Saint-Marc, maybe you would like to listen some of their musics. I remember that you told me you had read some biographies of composers, maybe you like the classical music? I'm intersted in it too, but I'm sure you know much more than me, do you have some good recommendaions?
</p>


<p>
"Neues finden - Neues schaffen", humm, you make me feel like learning some Germany during the summer vacation for a pleasure :-D And I always have a lot plans for my vacation about learning something, like swiming, pick up painting... But none of them has been put into reality yet :-D Maybe because I am always quite busy during the vacation... I hope this time will be different!
</p>


<p>
Now I'm doing my application for Visa on the internet, and it is necessary to write the exact time of Arriving and leaving, considering you have a vacation with your family in 1th September, maybe you need to go back to German a few days earlier, so I want to ask you what time do you prefer? The conference in Copenhagen end at 21th August, I'm Ok with all the time after that. What's more, I'm applying a Visa for visit instead of work, it that Ok for reimburse thing? I'm asking just to make sure I don't make any trouble for you, after all, it is a personal visit.
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-28 22:56]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-28-22-56/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:06+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-28-22-56</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Thu, 28 May 2015 22:56:59 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
yes, funny, isn't it, I also joked with my sister that one day, I will write a paper with her :-D But, who knows, what sounds far far away might really happen... At the moment, this is a bit like dreaming. As you say, the way is long. That's the case for my sister. But I really hope she will be happy, and that things will work out for her. It's my dearest wish. And I wish the same for you :-)
</p>


<p>
The project I told you about was actually very recent, we've been working on the book shortly until I left Germany. The book is to be published soon, we've sent the final version to the publisher. As you suspected, it's in German, the German title is "Neues finden - Neues schaffen". Translated it's something like "Find something new - create something new", although that doesn't sound as nice as the original title :-(
</p>


<p>
Yes, I agree, it's good to plan generously and to allow more time. Just to be on the safe side. Do you have to go to Paris then? I hope it'll be fine. In my case, when I applied for my visa for China, it was a mess. I needed a letter of invitation, and for some reason, the embassy didn't like the first version I got. So I had to get another one. In the end, I had to go to the embassy several times, and the people working there already knew my face and would greet me with a nod :-) Well, I hope that it will everything go smoothly for you. By the way, the visa fee can be reimbursed, just keep a receipt and give it to me afterwards.
</p>


<p>
Thanks for your congratulations :-) Yes, it's nice to be done with the exams. I look forward to enjoying life. And I already found time to watch Les Choristes. It's a movie with big feelings, I really like it a lot. I'm impressed how people can inspire people, and that being positive and good matters a lot. Also, music can be very powerful. Speaking about that, do you like to listen to music?
</p>


<p>
Best wishes, und gute Nacht,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-28 12:12]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-28-12-12/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:05+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-28-12-12</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Thursday, May 28, 2015 12:12 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Congratulations that you finished your task so efficiently, now I guess you could enjoy life again!
</p>


<p>
Your sister is going to a PhD in maths? Oh, that's wonderful! And this is must be a good news for you, I'm happy for you and I also happy for her that she has a brother like you ;-) Now I've already begun to imagine that in the future there would be two professor LI :-) If she could go to Cambridge, that would be fantastic, after all, this is a kind of "dream school" for most of us. And I'm sure that she will do excellent, because that's what she loves. I hope one day I could meet her.
</p>


<p>
Thank you for the article you sent, I like it, sometimes we can get many things in non-mathematical article written by mathmaticians. And the project you did seems interesting, you did it when you are still a student? You mentioned that your group write a book, what's its name? Althought it will most likely in Germany :-)
</p>


<p>
Yesterday, I looked up some informations about applying the Visa, it seems that althought the ducuments needed are quite simple, it still takes time to get my passport back, theoretically 30 days. So it will be better to preparing now in case I can't get my passport back before I go back to China.
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-27 19:06]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-27-19-06/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:04+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-27-19-06</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Wed, 27 May 2015 19:06:05 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I like your picture of mathematics. It actually reminds me of an article of Atiyah, who also compares mathematics with architecture. I've attached it, in case you are interested. Creativity is a fascinating subject, it is the beauty and challenge of mathematics at the same time. When I was in Germany, I took part in a project about creativity. The goal was to write a book discussing this topic from the perspective of all kinds of subjects. There were articles about creativity and biology, creativity and law, creativity and religion, creativity and music ..., and I also wrote something about creativity and mathematics. Moreover, we interviewed scientists and artists about their opinion. It was interesting to compare the roles creativity plays, and we realized that although the subjects are very different, there are common features. For instance that it's mysterious how we get ideas, they seem to come out of nowhere. But really, thinking about it, we realize that there is a long process of preparation (sometimes unconscious); that's what you describe as hard work.
</p>


<p>
Last weekend, my sister told me that she wants to a PhD in mathematics. It was quite a surprise for me, since last time we spoke, she was uncertain what she wants to do. But now she seems to be really determined. From my point of view, I just want her to find something she loves, any subject really, but that it will be mathematics is of course wonderful. My sister is now finishing her second year, and she plans to do her master in England, maybe in Cambridge. I hope that one day, you'll be able to meet her. I think that you two would have lots of things to talk about, since your situations are somewhat similar; and since your are more senior, my sister could learn something from you :-D
</p>


<p>
Yes, I just finished marking. This time it was quick: I started yesterday morning, and now I'm already done! Maybe the exam was too easy, or maybe my students really understood something *daydream*, or maybe I really wanted to answer your question with YES, but I was very efficient this time :-) I'm glad it's over.
</p>


<p>
Great that you like Papillon. It's funny that you mention the end, that's also my favourite part of the movie. I just felt so happy, because he was so determined, and longing so much to be free. Talking about determination, I was also impressed by the part where he is suffering so much in prison, isolated, in a narrow room, with almost no food, but still he wouldn't say the name of his friend. That's true friendship...
</p>


<p>
No no, you're not making any fuss at all, I'm actually glad that I have someone to tell the story, it's much better than keeping it to myself. And thanks for your warm words, they went straight into my heart, where I will keep them as a treasure. Thank you :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-26 15:24]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-26-15-24/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:03+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-26-15-24</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Tuesday, May 26, 2015 3:24 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Thank you so much for your reply, I always enjoy the way you talk about mathematics, it makes me feel encouraged and even enchanted sometimes:-) I consider doing mathematics as building a house, at first, you should build the fondation, this is something you should do with hard work, then the rest part of the house requires more other elements, like creativity. So I will go my way step by step with confidence.
</p>


<p>
I am happy that you tell me the story, in case you feel I'm making fuss, I shall say nothing except that: I believe you will do your best :-)
</p>


<p>
Speaking of old-fashioned, it's funny that this is the word I often use to describe myself, so I am glad I find a companion :-) Compared with kindle, I prefer the real books in fact, I enjoy the feeling of holding a book and turning the pages, which makes me feel tranquil. Anyway, hope you a good luck in the chinatown. By the way, have you finished marking?
</p>


<p>
I have wathched Papillon this weekend, I really like it, espacially the end of the movie. When he jumped into the sea with a bag of coconut shell, I think he got the real freeness no matter he succeeded or not...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-24 23:43]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-24-23-43/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:02+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-24-23-43</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Dimanche 24 Mai 2015 23:43:14
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I strongly believe that you can realize your dream of becoming a real mathematician. People seem to agree that the most important ingredients are hard work, passion and curiosity, and I see all these things in you. Of course there are other things like talent or luck, but these are not in our control. Actually, I never considered myself very talented. Luck I had several times, but everyone will get chances, so that's very normal. Honestly, I don't think that I did anything special, everyone can do it. And concerning your feeling that there is still a long way, yes, indeed, the way is long and not always easy, but every way consists of many many little steps, it's the same for everyone. I guess it's just important to keep moving, to be positive and to believe in yourself. And then, things will work out for you.
</p>


<p>
Here is the story behind this fifth talk: Some time ago, I was invited to apply for a professorship in Germany (starting in late 2016). It's at a good university, and I have great respect for one of the colleagues working there, it would be awesome to work with him. So I thought, I'd give it a try. Not that I'm unhappy here in London, it's just that the conditions in Germany are better, that's why it's so hard to get a permanent position there. Anyway, I applied, and didn't think too much about it since there is very little chance of success. However, when I was in Shanghai, I got a message saying that I made it into the second round, which means that I've been invited to give a talk and to an interview. That's the talk I mentioned. I still think that success is unlikely, but I'd like to try my best. To be honest, I haven't told anyone about this, not my colleagues, not even my parents or my sister, simply because it's unlikely, and I don't want to make a fuss. Please do me a favour and keep it as a secret, at least for now.
</p>


<p>
A Kindle? Do you like it? It's very convenient, of course. But is it the same feeling as a book? Maybe it's just me being old-fashioned :-) Anyway, I think I'll go to a bookstore in Chinatown, and try my luck there. I'll do it after I finished marking my exams. Marking is a horrible job, I really dislike it, so I need something nice to look forward to.
</p>


<p>
"And I wait for your reply just like a child wait for her present." You are so cute :-) Right now, several things are happening which might have a huge influence on my life. But one event stands out: That I have met you.
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-24 13:52]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-24-13-52/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:01+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-24-13-52</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Sunday, May 24, 2015 1:52 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
Reading your email can always put a big smile on my face, just like you said :-D And I wait for your reply just like a child wait for her present.
</p>


<p>
I feel that I have still a long way to go to become a real mathematician, maybe like you. But I really want to be one and I will try my best, your encouragement means a lot to me, thank you so much! Yes, I think giving a talk is also a way to help yourself understand better, I learned a lot last summer in Wuhan, we gave the talk in turns and discuss together, that's a good way to learn something. Talking about giving a lecture, your talk in Wuhan three weeks ago is great! I like it very much :-D (And, writing about this, I'm surprised to find out there are just two weeks since we said goodbye in Wuhan, time moves really slow indeed...) Your 5th talk will be a kind of special? Why?
</p>


<p>
In fact, the winner in Friday is one of my classmates in Master 2, now she's doing Phd in B too, but she does algebra and her talk is about the Hilbert series of pro-p group which I know few. But I am sure you know a lot.
</p>


<p>
As far as I know, buying Chinese literature in Europe is not an easy thing, I know a online Chinese bookstore in UK called Behomy, but I never tried, it has the same problem that there aren't many selections. However, in China, there are many good choices, I can find almost all the books I need in 当当 and Amazon china and the delivery is quite fast, maybe just two days I suppose, but it seems impossible to send the books to Europe. So every time I go back to China, I will bring some books to here, but the problem is it's a bit heavy... So, there is another choice. I bought a Kindle :-) The electronic edition of most of Chinese literature is available in Amazon China.
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-23 22:06]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-23-22-06/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:35:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-23-22-06</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Sat, 23 May 2015 22:06:32 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
I just want to say: Thank you, R, that you exist! Thank you so much! You make me happy. It's incredible, when I read an email from you, I feel like the happiest person in the world, but that feeling doesn't last very long, only until I get the next email from you, which makes me even happier :-)
</p>


<p>
I look forward, no, it is my dearest wish, to see you again. Why can't late August be already tomorrow? We talked about that time passes very quickly. But this is relative, if there is something we are longing for, then the time we have to wait can be extremely long, it never seems to pass. And three months is a very long time... I guess what helps is that we both will be busy over the summer: You will have this intensive working seminar in Wuhan, and an interesting conference in Copenhagen (these are the activities I know of); and I will go to four conferences, so that I will give four talks. In addition, I will give another fifth talk in some sort of seminar, but it's a bit special, and I really want to give a very good talk. So that will require some serious preparation. Concerning your visa, just make sure that you know the application procedure, and that you get your passport back immediately, so that you can travel directly afterwards. As always with these organizational things, they are annoying because they require time and energy, but in the end, they usually work out. So I'm sure you'll manage. Please keep me updated, so that we can make more concrete plans when the time is ripe. How wonderful it will be to meet you again...
</p>


<p>
Can I ask you a stupid question? What is the best way to buy Chinese books in Europe? Is it possible to do that online, so that the book is sent to my address? I tried some time ago, and realized that it's a non-trivial matter. For instance, European or American amazon has only a small selection of Chinese literature, and they are sold by some shops which might not be reliable. Do you know a better way?
</p>


<p>
It's great for PhD students to come together, and to give and listen to talks. What topics were the talks about? Anything in mathematics, or was the area more restricted? And what was the topic of the winner? Yes, giving a lesson seems like a very good idea. As long as it doesn't take too much time, it's good to practice giving talks. And usually, teaching helps to understand yourself. Actually, at some point, I'd like to listen to a talk by you about your research. Isn't that a wonderful thought? I'm confident that it will happen, and it would make me feel proud. You are very clever and hard-working, so just keep it up, and you'll do well :-)
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-22 20:39]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-22-20-39/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:59+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-22-20-39</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
From: r.x@e.fr &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Sent: Friday, May 22, 2015 8:39 PM
<br>
To: X L
<br>
Subject: Re : Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear X,
</p>


<p>
You are so nice and sweet! I'm happy that you still remember my question :-) In fact, I also looked up something about boomerang in the internet, but it explains in a professional way, I still couldn't understand after I read... So, thank you for your answer :-D.
</p>


<p>
I have read the poem of Hardy and the translation by Xu, it's really beautiful, then I can't stop reading them for several times...
</p>


<p>
You know, your email doesn't stop me being overexcited, but makes me even more exicited! And thank you very much for your generous offer, you give me so many good reasons that I can't even say no, so I guess I should accept it :-) Ok, back to reality, I'm thinking about applying my visa in the early July in Paris maybe one or two days before I take the plane back to China, because Besancon is a small city, there is no embassy. I hope everything will be fine.
</p>


<p>
Ah, ok, Papillion, I haven't heard it before, but it seems great, cause I watched The Shawshank Redemption few years ago which has the similar theme, and I love it, and I think your recommendation is even better, so I will watch it anyway.
</p>


<p>
Today, we went to "la journée de l'école doctorale" in D, some Ph.D. students gave interesting talks, and it's a good opportunity for me to learn how to give a lecture in French, because I thinking about giving a lesson next semester. And it's funny that the jury gave the winner 150€ as a gift.
</p>


<p>
Best,
<br>
R
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2015-05-21 21:30]]></title>
    <link href="http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-21-21-30/"/>
    <updated>2015-10-01T16:34:58+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://epitaph41love.github.io/blog/2015/10/01/2015-05-21-21-30</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>
De: "X L" &lt;x.l@q.uk&gt;
<br>
À: "r x" &lt;r.x@e.fr&gt;
<br>
Envoyé: Thu, 21 May 2015 21:30:21 +0200 (CEST)
<br>
Objet: Re: Re : Re: Merci beaucoup
</p>


<p>
Dear R,
</p>


<p>
and you have also said exactly the words I'd like to say :-) I also consider myself lucky that I can do what I really love to do. My work is for me just like a hobby, which I do out of interest and which I'm able to do for a living. This is actually one of the other main topics of Steve Job's Stanford speech I told you about; he said "You've got to find what you love. And that is as true for your work as it is for your lovers. Your work is going to fill a large part of your life, and the only way to be truly satisfied is to do what you believe is great work. And the only way to do great work is to love what you do. If you haven't found it yet, keep looking. Don't settle." It's so true. I'm happy it works for me. And I'm equally happy that you have found the same happiness :-)
</p>


<p>
Oh, if you could come to London in late August, that would be wonderful, truly great. Really, I mean it. London has a lot to offer, I could show you around, and we could go to Oxford, it's just a train ride away. But don't get overexcited, most likely, the dining hall in Christ Church will still be closed ;-) I guess it also applies to me; I have to stop myself from getting too excited, since you still have to sort out the visa issue. I hope that it'll be easy, and please let me know if I can be of any help. Before I forget: I'm going on vacation in Portugal with my parents and my sister from 1 September to 8 September, so planning your visit for late August is fine, but not later. Also, I'd be more than happy to pay for all your expenses and book accommodation on campus for you. The main reason is that I'd really love to do that from the bottom of my heart. But a more practical reason is that I have a grant which started this year, and a computation has shown that I have spent way to little money, although I already had this big trip to China and two visitors. So to save me some trouble, please do accept the offer.
</p>


<p>
Thanks for the poem, I like it a lot. Xu Zhimo also translated some English poems, for instance "A Week" by Hardy, very beautiful.
</p>


<p>
Actually, I meant another movie. It's just called Papillon, without Le, and it's older, from 1973. It's about a guy who has to go to prison for a crime he didn't commit. He then tries to escape ... Or in other words, it's about the desire to be free. I quite like it, maybe you would like it, too.
</p>


<p>
I like Harry Potter as well. Perhaps it's the child in everyone of us. Children have something fascinating and beautiful, they are without sorrows; I often have to smile when watching them play. Talking about playing, I looked up why a boomerang comes back, the secret is that the legs spin with different speed. Sorry if this sounds stupid, but I really liked that you asked me this question, and the way you asked it. So sweet :-) Maybe someone else would not have paid attention, but I somehow have kept this little incident as a memory, and now I'm caring it with me all the time ...
</p>


<p>
Best wishes,
<br>
X
</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
